<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drinktober 2021</title>
    <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Drinktober 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 12:07:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://drinktober.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>If you want beef then bring the ruckus</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/if-you-want-beef-then-bring-the-ruckus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/if-you-want-beef-then-bring-the-ruckus/</guid>
      <description>Another top act added to the bill for the Drinktober 2021 fundraising gig!
Bringing fresh C.R.E.A.M. from the dairies of Shaolin, these legendary bovine hip hop superstars ain&amp;rsquo;t nuthin to fuck wit. It&amp;rsquo;s the mighty Moo Tang Clan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONSUME</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/consume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/consume/</guid>
      <description>Aliens beware, I&amp;rsquo;m here to drink beer and kick ass - and I&amp;rsquo;ve nearly finished my beer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pompatus</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pompatus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pompatus/</guid>
      <description>Some people call me the Space Cowboy.
Some call me the Gangster of Love
But most people call me Jonny, because that&amp;rsquo;s like, my name, you know?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horsin&#39; Around</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/horsin-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/horsin-around/</guid>
      <description>Hitting the gym tonight and I&amp;rsquo;ve found the perfect recovery drink.
When you want to keep your workout stable, you can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with a little extra Horse Power!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whatever a spider can</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/whatever-a-spider-can/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/whatever-a-spider-can/</guid>
      <description>Today I&amp;rsquo;ve just been hanging out in my cool new black Spider suit which I&amp;rsquo;m sure isn&amp;rsquo;t secretly evil or anything! Here&amp;rsquo;s hoping I don&amp;rsquo;t find myself caught up in its Dark Web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master of Beasts</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/master-of-beasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/master-of-beasts/</guid>
      <description>A mighty warrior approaches for today&amp;rsquo;s Drinktober.
Riding through the wilderness atop Maui, his fearsome battle hedgehog comes the mighty Beast Master. This unstoppable barbarian hero lives only for vengeance - and beer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pump it up a little more</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pump-it-up-a-little-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pump-it-up-a-little-more/</guid>
      <description>Lock up your pantries!
That rascally rogue Jam Master Jonny is on the loose again, roaming across town with his bicycle pump. No fruity preserve is safe from his deranged mission to Pump Up The Jam!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarr</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/yarr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/yarr/</guid>
      <description>Arr, it be a tough life on the seven seas, sometimes when the looting and plundering hits a quiet spell it can be hard for a cap&amp;rsquo;n to keep up with all his streaming subscriptions.
If ye don&amp;rsquo;t want yer crew to mutiny on account of not being able to get Disney+ ye might have to sail the dangerous waters of the Pirate Bay&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Chopper</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/big-chopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/big-chopper/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m taking a break from it all in my cabin in the woods, but would you believe it? The ring pulls on all the beer I brought with me have snapped off, leaving me unable to open them!!
Luckily I came prepared - I just need to introduce the cans to my Axe Edge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even more pew!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/even-more-pew/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/even-more-pew/</guid>
      <description>If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing we love here at Drinktober, it&amp;rsquo;s shamelessly reusing the same prop twice and calling it a storyline :)
I thought I&amp;rsquo;d finally fought off the invaders, but this last one turned out to be too much for me to handle.
Now my only chance to survive is if I can Escape the Mothership!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pew! Pew!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pew-pew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pew-pew/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been overrun by Space Invaders!
Luckily I&amp;rsquo;ve got my trusty laser rifle at hand but they just keep on coming, Wave After Wave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t panic! At the Disco</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/don-t-panic-at-the-disco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/don-t-panic-at-the-disco/</guid>
      <description>It may be Sunday but here at Drinktober towers we&amp;rsquo;re still feeling the Saturday Night Fever.
Time to bust out the shiny balls and hit the floor to some tasty beats from the Disco King!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelations and Carvery  </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/revelations-and-carvery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/revelations-and-carvery/</guid>
      <description>Another day, more water and Heineken Zero! I also appear to have replaced vino with food considering the amount of carvery I’ve put away today.
I&amp;rsquo;ve had a weekend of sleep, reading and revelations being by myself and sober. Some of my closer people know this has been a bit of a mad year for me with a lot of anxiety and change, but apparently it appears that I actually quite enjoy being by myself and I don’t need anyone to meet my needs or look after me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Born in the Moo S E</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/born-in-the-moo-s-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/born-in-the-moo-s-e/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve attracted some top talent for this year&amp;rsquo;s Drinktober!
Book your tickets now for our epic fundraising concert, featuring top hits like &amp;ldquo;Born to Ruminate&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Antlers in the Dark&amp;rdquo;, by the mighty, the majestic, the magnificent : Moose Springsteen!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not yet a Cat-astrophe 🐈‍⬛ </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/not-yet-a-ca-tastrophe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/not-yet-a-ca-tastrophe/</guid>
      <description>Day 2! 💪
Fiyero (AKA Mr Fifi) is enthralled by this new beer which doesnt make mother fall over.
A day of crazy pirate mini golfing was cancelled due to me a) still being sick af and b) the usual rain of the North. So instead of hitting the pub with my homies, I have scrubbed a floor, eaten lasagne with my neighbours, eaten the worlds hottest noodles (TM) and stayed off the booze!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beers don&#39;t hit back</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/beers-don-t-hit-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/beers-don-t-hit-back/</guid>
      <description>And we&amp;rsquo;re off! Welcome back to another month of the booze-inspired mayhem known as Drinktober. We&amp;rsquo;ve got some absolutely phenomenal stuff coming up this year so get ready to go hammer on that donate button!
Kicking things off with a kung fu classic as I whip out my trusty beer-chucks and prepare to Enter the Dragon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Zero to Hero (ish)!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/from-zero-to-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/from-zero-to-hero/</guid>
      <description>Look at that artistic photo! The colour, the style, the Asthetic! 📸
Some of you might know this has been a bit of a mad year for me, certainly not one I was expecting, and one I have certainly hit the bar amongst other things pretty bloody hard. So this year will probably be my biggest challenge yet.
Kicking it off today is this flirty little Heineken 0.0 delight, served with a bloody amazing steak sandwich at my favourite establishment The Punch Hotel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep taking the pils </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/keep-taking-the-pils/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/keep-taking-the-pils/</guid>
      <description>Droogies, boozers, strumpets and losers! Welcome once more to the booziest charity event of the year : Drinktober!
It&amp;rsquo;s been a loooooong year, but we&amp;rsquo;ve made it this far and it&amp;rsquo;s time to have some fun (well, it&amp;rsquo;s time for me to have some fun. Poor Heidi gets to spend a month on the wagon while I muck about and have a laugh.)
This year we&amp;rsquo;re going even bigger and even better, with more beers, sillier antics, and a bumper crop of poor-quality cosplay, so watch this space and get ready to chuck some cash in the pot and make all this nonsense worthwhile!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s all folks</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/that-s-all-folks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/that-s-all-folks/</guid>
      <description>For the twelfth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Twelve Days original porter from Hook Norton.
And so the twelve beers of Christmas comes to an end - I hope it&amp;rsquo;s been as much fun for you guys as it has for me. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to hit the donate button on your way out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting blitzed</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/getting-blitzed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/getting-blitzed/</guid>
      <description>For the eleventh beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Blitzen Ruby Christmas Ale from Black Sheep
We&amp;rsquo;re almost at the end now, so it seems like a good time to celebrate with this famous festive special from the kebab shop - Döner and Blitzen :D</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pony play</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/pony-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/pony-play/</guid>
      <description>For the tenth day of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : My Little Sabrony from Arbor Ales
It&amp;rsquo;s been a tough old year, a bit of a &amp;lsquo;mare. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s tricky to stay stable. A little horsing around once in a while can help save you from _foal_ing apart at the seams.
If you&amp;rsquo;re still reading after those dreadful horse puns, why not hoof it over to the donation page and drop a few quid in the box?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enter the ouch mouse!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/enter-the-ouch-mouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/enter-the-ouch-mouse/</guid>
      <description>For the ninth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Pricky Back Otchan from Great Newsome Brewery
According to the label, the Pricky Back Otchan is the old Yorkshire name for a hedgehog, so naturally I had to bring out superstar hedgehog Princess Neville to take her turn in the spotlight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But I&#39;d have to charge</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/but-i-d-have-to-charge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/but-i-d-have-to-charge/</guid>
      <description>For the eighth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Off Tempo Milkshake IPA from Bad Co. brewing
Normally this milkshake IPA would bring all the boys to the yard, but due to social distancing it&amp;rsquo;s running online milkshake classes instead.
A shiny no-prize goes to the first person to identify all the &amp;ldquo;boys&amp;rdquo; on the zoom call&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is the way</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/this-is-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/this-is-the-way/</guid>
      <description>For the seventh beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Easy Now Baby NEIPA from Bad Co. Brewing
It&amp;rsquo;s the eighth day of Drinkmas - New Beer&amp;rsquo;s Eve - and I&amp;rsquo;m stretching the theme to it&amp;rsquo;s limits in a flagrant case of wanting an excuse to make a costume. Baby IPA, Baby Yoda - close enough, right!
Guest starring Selwyn as the not very convincing Grogu in an undersized cardboard pod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meow</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/meow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/meow/</guid>
      <description>For the sixth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Christmas Kitty vanilla porter from Brass Castle
That&amp;rsquo;s right, the Christmas Kitty has come to visit - that well known festive tradition that we all know about. Or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a deleted scene from the Cats movie?
Either way - meow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jingle</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/jingle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/jingle/</guid>
      <description>For the fifth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Jingle Bell Rock golden ale from Pennine Brewing Co.
So occasionally when people see the Beercave Christmas decorations they ask &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s with the large paper boulder with the bells glued to it?&amp;rdquo;
So I tell them : &amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s the Jingle Bell Rock!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He sees you when you&#39;re sleeping..</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/he-sees-you-when-you-re-sleeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/he-sees-you-when-you-re-sleeping/</guid>
      <description>For the fourth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman gave to me - Evil Elf biscuity ale, from Rudgate.
 He sees you when you&amp;rsquo;re sleeping
He&amp;rsquo;s watching from his shelf
He wants to cut you inside out
So beware the Evil Elf!
 Yes, here to spread a little Christmas fear, it&amp;rsquo;s the evil elf. He&amp;rsquo;s off the shelf, off the chain, and out for blood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dej-arr vu!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/dej-arr-vu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/dej-arr-vu/</guid>
      <description>For the third beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman gave to me - Anchor Christmas Ale!
And so, from the Department of Shameless prop re-use, here&amp;rsquo;s a Christmas Anchor.
Yo-Ho-Ho-Ho!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When elves go bad</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/when-elves-go-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/when-elves-go-bad/</guid>
      <description>For the second beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman gave to me, a Bad Elf dry hop ale.
So it looks like I was one present short yesterday, and now I know why! I found this cheeky little character sitting on his shelf&amp;hellip; and he&amp;rsquo;s nicked my beer!
That&amp;rsquo;s what I call a Bad Elf!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say Merry Christmas to my little friend!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/say-merry-christmas-to-my-little-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/say-merry-christmas-to-my-little-friend/</guid>
      <description>For the first beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman gave to me, a White Christmas ale from Saltaire brewery.
There may not be snow on the ground, but Tony Montana here has his own ideas about how to enjoy a white Christmas&amp;hellip;
Merry Christmas, ya cock-a-roaches!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beer we go again </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/beer-we-go-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/beer-we-go-again/</guid>
      <description>Well, here we are again, back between the bottle and the glue gun for a festive Drinktober special edition.
When Heidi&amp;rsquo;s not engaged in alcohol free antics, she also rules over Hull LGBT+ Community Pride, AKA Pride in Hull with her tiny iron fist - or something along those lines anyway! So when she mentioned raising funds for their 2021 event I jumped at the opportunity to drink beer and show off :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The End?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/the-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/the-end/</guid>
      <description>So, that&amp;rsquo;s about it for Drinktober 2020 then. I don&amp;rsquo;t know about you guys, but I&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of fun. I&amp;rsquo;m already starting to plot next year&amp;rsquo;s antics, I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to pull out quite a few stops if I want to top this one!
As always, the donation site will be open for a while yet, so if you&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to chuck something in the pot and haven&amp;rsquo;t got around to it yet there&amp;rsquo;s still time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT IS DONE!! </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/it-is-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/it-is-done/</guid>
      <description>IT 👏 IS 👏 DONE 👏
I waited until 12 to have a prosecco&amp;hellip;..but after 2 glasses I’m done, I don’t even want to get lashed!
Possibly the weirdest DrinkTober yet, with covid and a new lockdown as of today, but I’m actually feeling quite good. This is the year I’ve actually enjoyed the break and felt more comfortable to not drink. Im proud of myself and feeling quite grown up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t fear the reaper</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/don-t-fear-the-reaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/don-t-fear-the-reaper/</guid>
      <description>And so at last we come to the final night of Drinktober 2020. It&amp;rsquo;s Drinkowe&amp;rsquo;en - the drunkest, spookiest night of the year!
I hope you&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed my ridiculous antics all month - we&amp;rsquo;re still a long way from the target so if you&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about making a donation now&amp;rsquo;s the time to hit that link over there, right under Heidi.
As for me, I&amp;rsquo;m going to enjoy a nice quiet drink outdoors - in the Garden of Death!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art of darkness</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/art-of-darkness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/art-of-darkness/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s Satanic encounter left quite an impression on me.
Now that I&amp;rsquo;m in league with the forces of evil, I&amp;rsquo;ve retreated to Ye Olde Wizarding Shoppe where I&amp;rsquo;ve been dabbling in the Dart Arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So _CLOSE_ </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/so-_close_/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/so-_close_/</guid>
      <description>It’s so bloody close!!
one more day to go. I was initially not looking forward to this October, but I’ve surprisingly enjoyed it in a funny way. Covid times are weird, so getting out walking and away from boredom drinking In front of the telly has been great (Although no walking for me for a few days due to getting a massive tattoo on my foot Yesterday!)
Overall I’m looking forward to a little drink when I finish, but I’m proud of myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horny</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/horny/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/horny/</guid>
      <description>Tonight finds me working on a &amp;ldquo;special&amp;rdquo; batch of homebrew for Drinkowe&amp;rsquo;en - this terrifying concoction was made under the influence of dark forces beyond my control.
It&amp;rsquo;s not my fault - the Devil made me brew it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does exactly what it says on the tin</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/does-exactly-what-it-says-on-the-tin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/does-exactly-what-it-says-on-the-tin/</guid>
      <description>What more can I say about the ghastly skeletal presence that&amp;rsquo;s appeared to host tonight&amp;rsquo;s thrilling episode?
With that massive ivory bonce, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty clear he&amp;rsquo;s a bit of a Bonehead!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rather have a piece of toast</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/rather-have-a-piece-of-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/rather-have-a-piece-of-toast/</guid>
      <description>A terrifying presence arises as the spooky shenanigans continue.
I&amp;rsquo;m being haunted by a spooky ghost - and he&amp;rsquo;s nicked my beer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little goody two-shoes!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/little-goody-two-shoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/little-goody-two-shoes/</guid>
      <description>What has Science wrought?
The synaptic transmitter was more successful than I could have imagined, but now I&amp;rsquo;m face to face with my Evil Twin! But which one is Good Jonny, and which is Bad Jonny?
Good? Bad? I&amp;rsquo;m the one with the beer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the rocks</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/on-the-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/on-the-rocks/</guid>
      <description>I like a southern comfort or a brandy on the rocks, even a cheeky gin ting too. Yesterday I was on different rocks!
Apparently when I don’t spend my sundays in the pub or cleaning, I enjoy outdoors now. Even getting muddy and climbing up waterfalls, j loved it! I’m even considering buying walking boots, what’s that all about? The none drinking has helped me go out and explore and actually move which I am enjoying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s alive! Alive!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/it-s-alive-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/it-s-alive-alive/</guid>
      <description>The mad science continues in tonight&amp;rsquo;s instalment, as I test out my new Synaptic Transmission device.
Can the machine transfer my mind and bring the construct to life? We&amp;rsquo;ll just have to wait and see&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do you wanna get high?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/do-you-wanna-get-high/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/do-you-wanna-get-high/</guid>
      <description>Tonight I&amp;rsquo;m putting the fun back into funambulism, taking to the skies to walk the high wire!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 days, 7 miles </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/7-days-7-miles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/7-days-7-miles/</guid>
      <description>Only 7 days to go!! It feels like it’s gone super fast this year. On the theme of 7’s&amp;hellip;.. I lost another 7lbs this week, so celebrated by going for a 7 mile walk. And it RAINNNNNED. I got piss wet through, but persevered, like I have with my sober challenge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It always brings me down</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/it-always-brings-me-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/it-always-brings-me-down/</guid>
      <description>Tonight sees me back in the lab and testing out my latest invention - this handy, compact anti-gravity machine, which is definitely a brand new invention and not the dream machine with a new label hastily taped to the front!
As you can see, things got away from me during the first test - my beer drifted away, torn from my hands by the Wild Gravity!
It&amp;rsquo;s true what they say- gravity is a harsh mistress!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where’s October? </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/where-s-october/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/where-s-october/</guid>
      <description>Where the hell has October gone?! A week and a day to go until normality can resume. Today was manic and I didn’t atop, but I didn’t actually think about having a drink, even though I had a night to myself when I’d usually treat myself. That’s personal growth right there lads!
We’ve not had many donations this year, despite Johnny making it the highest class DrinkTober yet. So thank you to those that have donated, and the rest of you get your hands in your pockets!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kart load of ale!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/kart-load-of-ale/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/kart-load-of-ale/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s-a-me! Jonny-O!
Tonight finds me racing on that most fiendish of tracks - the Rainbow Road. Luckily I&amp;rsquo;ve got a good supply of IPA power-ups to help fend off the roaming Goombas!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Passenger</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/dark-passenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/dark-passenger/</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of names for what I do. Monster. Maniac. Serial killer.
All I know is, if you find yourself strapped to my table, the world would be a better place without you.
So what does that make me? Am I an avenging angel? The hero this city deserves? Or just another American Psycho?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smokin&#39;</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/smokin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/smokin/</guid>
      <description>Some smoked beer really demands some smoked food to go with it, so I fired up the BBQ in the midst of October in East Yorkshire (hey, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t raining! perfect weather!) with some homemade sausage and a chicken. Very tasty it was too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pub ahoy! </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/pub-ahoy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/pub-ahoy/</guid>
      <description>The ultimate challenge has occurred: had a meeting in the pub tonight after work. But, I stayed strong; and had 2 diet cokes! Which weirdly are more expensive than a pint, but hey ho still cheaper than moet.
I also resisted fish and chips, my only greater love than wine, so I’m chuffed I managed that despite being up at 6 with my dad been taken to a&amp;amp;e and work all day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So tired. So sober. </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/so-tired.so-sober/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/so-tired.so-sober/</guid>
      <description>Sooooooo tired and I have no energy! Went to give blood Today and it’s the first time it’s not been a great excuse to get drunk quicker! Overall I’m feeling better not drinking but I’m struggling to stay awake tonight: I reckon one vodka would currently knock me out anyway so I guess Viva le Sober!
Also on the subject of unconventional tattoos&amp;hellip;. I’ve booked one with all the money I saved not drinking 😂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stabby Stabby</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/stabby-stabby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/stabby-stabby/</guid>
      <description>What better way to celebrate the best Drinktober yet than with some commemorative body art?
I&amp;rsquo;m starting to think maybe the &amp;ldquo;Ink and Dagger Tattoo Parlour&amp;rdquo; might not have been the best choice though&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aren&#39;t you a little drunk for a Stromtrooper?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/aren-t-you-a-little-drunk-for-a-stromtrooper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/aren-t-you-a-little-drunk-for-a-stromtrooper/</guid>
      <description>A long time ago, in a galaxy far, far away&amp;hellip; I had a beer.
Tonight&amp;rsquo;s thrilling drinktober instalment sees me transported far across the galaxy and recruited into the Imperial legions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a machine </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/i-am-a-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/i-am-a-machine/</guid>
      <description>Hola! Works been stressful and last night I struggled a lot to not drink.
Butttttt, today I got weighed and I’ve lost 6lbs, taking my total to 16lbs which made me feel better! Went walking and managed 8.2 miles today, meaning I don’t fancy a drink at all tonight!
Please take a moment to donate if you can, my legs might drop off from today’s wandering so a cheeky fiver whilst I’m infirm would be 👌</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goblin it all up</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/goblin-it-all-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/goblin-it-all-up/</guid>
      <description>See the little goblin, see his little feet!
And his little nosey-wose, isn&amp;rsquo;t the goblin sweet? Yes!
The little goblin drinking song
 A creepy figure tends to his hoard for tonight&amp;rsquo;s installment of Drinktober.
Beware all you who would seek the Hobgoblin Gold, for you may find great riches but you will never escape the curse of the Wych Wood!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tetris Terrors!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/tetris-terrors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/tetris-terrors/</guid>
      <description>Back to the antics and facing almost certain doom tonight.
I&amp;rsquo;ve arranged all these glowing blocks into a neat pattern, and for my troubles I&amp;rsquo;m about to be crushed under this giant beer! I guess that&amp;rsquo;ll teach me to try to Tessellate&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Please God give me a gin.</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/please-god-give-me-a-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/please-god-give-me-a-gin/</guid>
      <description>Jesus Christ I wanted a drink tonight!! I could on practically taste it. I spent a moment gazing at the prosecco at my corner shop waving my bank card and probably looked a bit not ok.
Frustrating day of stupid Expensive internet Dropping out and losing my work, followed by a 2 hour rowing with a smart plug which wouldn’t work and I would probably kill your nan for a drink about now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the grass is green</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/where-the-grass-is-green/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/where-the-grass-is-green/</guid>
      <description>Bit of a quiet one for the 15th of Drinktober. Tonight I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying a can of Paradise City from Tiny Rebel :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet dreams are made of beer</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/sweet-dreams-are-made-of-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/sweet-dreams-are-made-of-beer/</guid>
      <description>Who am I to disagree?
I&amp;rsquo;ve been hard at work in my secret lab working on this latest invention.
Now, by harnessing the power of SCIENCE!!! my Dream Machine allows me to see inside my dreams. The results are&amp;hellip; well, somewhat predictable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well Jesus Christ </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/well-jesus-christ/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/well-jesus-christ/</guid>
      <description>Well, that was a few days. Sent to work from home because I’ve developed a bizarre hives like rash type affair EVERYWHERE&amp;hellip;.. which apparently is a covid sign. Also, I’ve developed random sporadic vomiting today, WITHOUT EVEN HAVING AN ALCOHOL. Wtf?!!
So I am currently very itchy, a bit nauseous, and with a headache from 11 and a half hours on zoom meeting, and a little drink would be bloody fantastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s better than some beer?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/what-s-better-than-some-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/what-s-better-than-some-beer/</guid>
      <description>More beer more beer more beer more!
Drink! Drink! Drink! Till you drink no more!
Ravenage - More beer
 Almost 2 weeks into Drinktober and it&amp;rsquo;s been quite a ride so far. As you can see, all this beer is starting to take it&amp;rsquo;s toll, so there&amp;rsquo;s only one thing that can fix it&amp;hellip;
MORE BEER!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wilmaaaaaaaaa!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/wilmaaaaaaaaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/wilmaaaaaaaaa/</guid>
      <description>Another trip back in time for the 12th of Drinktober. It&amp;rsquo;s clocking-off time in Bedrock so I&amp;rsquo;m sliding down the back of my dinosaur ready to head home.
Yabbadabbadoo!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zzzzz</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/zzzzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/zzzzz/</guid>
      <description>Day counts on fingers 12, almost 13!! And I’m surprisingly ok, barring the odd “oh I could have a glass of&amp;hellip;.never mind” thoughts I’m alright! I’m tired, but less tired than usual. This is the first year I’ve not been tearing my hair out by week 2, I’m shocked how well I’m doing!? Someone have a party and tempt me to make it harder, I’m sick of grouting things!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For those about to drink</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/for-those-about-to-drink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/for-those-about-to-drink/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;Cause I shoot to thrill, and I&amp;rsquo;m ready to kill
I can&amp;rsquo;t get enough, I can&amp;rsquo;t get my fill
I shoot to thrill, play to kill
Yeah, pull the trigger
AC/DC - Shoot to Thrill
 Tonight I&amp;rsquo;m crashing the stage with rock legends AC/DC to fire my Big Gun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do you like movies about gladiators?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/do-you-like-movies-about-gladiators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/do-you-like-movies-about-gladiators/</guid>
      <description>My name is Citrus Maxima. Commander of the armies of the Hops. General of the zesty Legions, loyal servant of the brew Emperor.
Drinker of a finished pint, holder of an empty glass.
And I will have my beer, in this pub or the next!
 Stepping back in time for the 10th of Drinktober, to the days of Ancient Rome, where the mighty gladiator Citrus Maxima conquered the arena and toppled an empire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never walked in my life unless it’s to the pub</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/never-walked-in-my-life-unless-it-s-to-the-pub/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/never-walked-in-my-life-unless-it-s-to-the-pub/</guid>
      <description>I am back! Didn’t post yesterday because I managed to lock myself out of the website: something that’s a common occurrence when drunk but I’m not sure how I managed it sober.
10 whole days in and I’ve lost 10lbs which is rather nice. Can’t say I’ve saved money because my house is falling down but still, I’ll take it! Today as oppose to my usual leisurely walk to the pub (the extent of my normal walking) I went on an actual solo wander which ended up being quite a treck through a housing estate, a tiny forest, some nice hills and some ropey garages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ich habe Space Dementia</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/ich-habe-space-dementia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/ich-habe-space-dementia/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s that there? I don&amp;rsquo;t care
Sat alone, with no cards, playing solitaire
Breathe cold air, fuel&amp;rsquo;s spent yeah
Ich habe space dementia
Space Dementia, Evil Scarecrow
 I&amp;rsquo;ve been blasted into the deep space for the 9th of Drinktober, courtesy of Arbor Ales&#39; Space Hardware.
I think the isolation has sent me a bit funny - am I really seeing Neville the space hedgehog or has my mind succumbed to Space Dementia?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All cracked up</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/all-cracked-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/all-cracked-up/</guid>
      <description>This wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite what I meant by a night on the tiles!
For the 8th of Drinktober, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a nice big can of Mosaic ale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I need you to kill me. </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/i-need-you-to-kill-me./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/i-need-you-to-kill-me./</guid>
      <description>I really fancy a booze tbh. I’ve had a bastardo of a day, I’ve not stopped and I’m still on the grouting mission so everything hurts and I would put my face through a window for a little vat of wine. I could drink it in the bath when I look at my grout.
send help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All washed up</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/all-washed-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/all-washed-up/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been attacked by sea monsters, and hurled into the deep by an ungrateful crew, but at last, my nautical adventure comes to a happy ending, as I&amp;rsquo;ve washed up on this Tropical island.
Now to enjoy a few tasty beers among the palm trees with my little parrot buddy Iago.
Cheers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A worrying development </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/a-worrying-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/a-worrying-development/</guid>
      <description>Today’s the first day I fancied a drink, which had led to a somewhat worrying development.
To keep me occupied, I have now replaced having a relaxing glass of wine with DIY. Today we have had a light fitted, ripped down a ceiling and it’s now 11pm and I’m removing all the grout from the bathroom tiles.
Is this healthy? Where will this end?
Will we survive?!!!!
Also my feet hurt, my hand is black And I have a significant amount of plaster in my hair and tit region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutiny!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/mutiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/mutiny/</guid>
      <description>Gather round and listen to this tale of treachery upon the high seas.
It seems my shipmates took offence to my language yesterday, in the middle of the night those mutinous dogs dragged me from my bunk and tossed me overboard.
I managed to save myself from Davey Jones&#39; locker by lashing a raft together from some driftwood, but now I&amp;rsquo;m a castaway, adrift upon the Big Sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>With a what now?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/with-a-what-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/with-a-what-now/</guid>
      <description>Fuck! You! You&amp;rsquo;re a fucking wanker! We&amp;rsquo;re gonna punch you right in the balls!
Fuck! You! With a fucking anchor! You&amp;rsquo;re all cunts so fuck you all!
Alestorm - Fucked with an anchor
 Stretching the theme a little bit for the 5th of Drinktober, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist the opportunity to combine three of my favourite things. Pirate costumes, heavy metal and gratuitous swearing!
Sing along, ye scurvy dogs!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well that was a challenge </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/well-that-was-a-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/well-that-was-a-challenge/</guid>
      <description>I’ve survived a challenge!
Most of you people know I’m a little&amp;hellip;.. funny. I’m quite OCD and if things aren’t right or tidy, expect a breakdown. I’m also an emotional drinker: annoyed? Have a brandy. Happy? Have a champers. Stressed? Vat of wine and an absolut chaser.
So yesterday I didn’t manage a post, but I did have half my kitchen ceiling down fixing a leaking lead pipe, plaster all over, half my bathroom taken out and no electric due to my dodge lighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to get Loco!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/it-s-time-to-get-loco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/it-s-time-to-get-loco/</guid>
      <description>For the 4th of Drinktober we step into the ring with the mighty El Loco - the most feared luchador in all of East Yorkshire!
Undefeated in every match, this fearsome hero of the ring strikes terror into the hearts of his opponents, and loves nothing more than to celebrate a successful match with a victory beer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water leaks from the ceiling and you also have to drink it </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/water-leaks-from-the-ceiling-and-you-have-to-drink-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/water-leaks-from-the-ceiling-and-you-have-to-drink-it/</guid>
      <description>Ok day three, whatcha got?
Well we all know I’m a prolific stress drinker. So today I had a small paddy that my house is essentially falling down, nothing works and my pipes (Which are leaking) are made of lead (apparently this is bad). So I realllllly fancied some wine, or 9 double vodkas of something .
However, I’ve stayed strong and drank water all goddamn day. Which is slightly less appealing to drink when it’s slowly dripping from your ceiling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a lovely day!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/what-a-lovely-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/what-a-lovely-day/</guid>
      <description>Beer. Beer never changes.
When the old world fell, only a few survived. Roaming the blacktop between the remnants of the cities, scavenging for the last remaining booze of a lost civilisation.
A drop of ale in the wasteland can help keep a man sane - because if you don&amp;rsquo;t keep your head&amp;hellip; you&amp;rsquo;re nothing but Roadkill&amp;hellip;
 Things are going a little bit post-apocalyptic for the 3rd of Drinktober as I take to the roads of the blasted wasteland that was once Yorkshire in search of more beer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking a little pale</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/looking-a-little-pale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/looking-a-little-pale/</guid>
      <description>A fairly quiet one for the second of Drinktober. I&amp;rsquo;m hard at work in the Beercave prepping for the insanity to come, just taking a break to enjoy a tasty Rudgate Pale.
Tune in tomorrow, same beer time, same beer channel, when we start to kick things up a notch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAY 2! </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2, feeling confident! Day one was a piece of piss because I was ill, so I slept through my normal drinking time! So far today I’m on 5 coffees, a herbal tea and 4 waters, might be piddling for England but sober af! 🙌🏻</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back once again with the Drunken Master</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/back-once-again-with-the-drunken-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/back-once-again-with-the-drunken-master/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first of Drinktober, and I should be working hard on getting everything set up for this year&amp;rsquo;s shenanigans, but instead here I am just chilling in my hammock with a nice cold lager.
I guess I&amp;rsquo;m just a Lazy Boy ;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drinktober 2020 Trailer</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/drinktober-2020-trailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/drinktober-2020-trailer/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the official video trailer for Drinktober 2020. Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drinktober 2020 - Lockdown lock-in!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/drinktober-2020-lockdown-lock-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/drinktober-2020-lockdown-lock-in/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to Drinktober 2020 - we&amp;rsquo;re having a lock-in! Or a lockdown! Hopefully not getting locked up&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;m not the type to let a little thing like a global pandemic, or impending political and economic collapse get in the way of a good time, so Drinktober 2020 is going ahead as scheduled.
I&amp;rsquo;ve got an exciting range of beers lined up thanks to the excellent chaps at Beer Bandits, conveniently located just down the road from me, and lots of extremely silly antics planned, so watch this space and ready your wallets for the biggest Drinktober yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And that&#39;s a wrap</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/and-that-s-a-wrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/and-that-s-a-wrap/</guid>
      <description>So there we have it, folks. Another year of #Drinktober comes to a close, and we absolutely smashed it this time around.
Donations are currently sitting at 110% of the fundraising target, Heidi&amp;rsquo;s swanned off to Tenerife to drink her body weight in Prosecco, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to sign off until we come back even bigger and better for Drinktober 2020!
Watch this space!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s only chuffing DONE! </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/it-s-only-chuffing-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/it-s-only-chuffing-done/</guid>
      <description>Well, it’s done!! And what a bloody month. Here’s what I learned:
  I don’t need alcohol, but I DO have the most stressful life and I don’t take enough time out. The past 2 weeks at work were hard. Not having a drink made me realise my job can be emotionally draining. I have little time for myself and I take on too much without thinking about unwinding in a better way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 31 - Drinkoween!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-31-drinkoween/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-31-drinkoween/</guid>
      <description>Gee, Jonny, what are we going to do tonight?
Same thing we do every night - D̗͖͖͓̹͎̃ͦ̒ͨ̅͊̀͢ͅR̵͂̚͏͕̠̘I̲̰͉̊̑͐͆ͧ͐̍̉̽N̶̼̻̩ͭ́ͨͭ̔͑̽͢͞K̴̶̼̰͓͓̲͗̆̈́ͫ̉̌͆͢ ͈͈͓͙̉ͭ̂͒͝B̛̬̪͔̻̖̃̑ͭ̀ͪͯͪͦ͢͞E̷̲̘̞͋ͩ̀̕E̵̓̎ͭ̓̈́̐̾ͫ҉̛̭͙̩͍R̮͈̎́̓̉ͪ ͈̪̬̘͎̣̬̩͆̿ͪͧ͌̉̚͞A̖̖ͨN̸͉̺͕̥̫ͬ̄́̐̏ͪD̺̞̪̩͍ͦͬ̀ ̨̡͈̲͈̤̞͛͋ͥ̍H̻̪̮̪̞̹͇̾ͮ̂͜͠ͅA̸̧̙̮̥̟̭̔̆̽̊̈́ͅỈ̧̦͕͇͕̄̋̿ͮͨ̀L̠̹̣̗̰̟͉͐̂̓͑͜͠ ̨̠͈͇̫͈̼̗ͯ̓́S̷̼̯̱ͥͥ̄ͩͤ̔̌ͅA͂͐ͬ͊ͩ͂̚͠҉͔̜͕͔̻̝͍͖Ṭ̥̒̆̕A̭̞̣̎̉͋ͥͥ̄͌̑̓͞N̘̮̱̖̖̪̝͚̯ͩ̋̐͐͑ͥ̆ͫ͢͜!ͦ́̋̾҉̴͓
 We&amp;rsquo;ve reached once again, the final night of #Drinktober -Drinkowe&amp;rsquo;en is here! Seemed only right to see the end with the most evil beer I could lay my hands on&amp;hellip;
If you&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed my ridiculous antics all month, why not click on the link over there -&amp;gt; (or down below if you&amp;rsquo;re on mobile) and donate a few bob for the real hero of Drinktober.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 30 - Bustin&#39; makes me feel good</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-30-bustin-makes-me-feel-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-30-bustin-makes-me-feel-good/</guid>
      <description>These supernatural incursions have been getting out of hand. Time to bust out my trusty proton pack for the 30th of #Drinktober and send them all back to Spookytown!
Join us again tomorrow night for the final frightfest of #Drinktober 2019 - Drinkowe&amp;rsquo;en!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 29 - When there&#39;s no more room in hell</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-29-when-there-s-no-more-room-in-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-29-when-there-s-no-more-room-in-hell/</guid>
      <description>The horror continues on the 29th of #Drinktober as the dead rise from their graves to walk the earth in a never-ending quest for beer. Beware, the terrors of the Graveyard Shift!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 28 - They&#39;ll get yours in the end!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-28-they-ll-get-yours-in-the-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-28-they-ll-get-yours-in-the-end/</guid>
      <description>Spooky creatures of the night seem to be everywhere on the 28th of #Drinktober - I just caught this Gangly Ghoul sneaking a snack from the fridge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 27 - You remind me of the Babe</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-27-you-remind-me-of-the-babe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-27-you-remind-me-of-the-babe/</guid>
      <description>Another monstrous creature appears for the 27th of #Drinktober - emerging from his haunted skull cave comes the evil King Goblin!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 26 - Sky is turning red!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-26-sky-is-turning-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-26-sky-is-turning-red/</guid>
      <description>Frightening scenes for the 26th of #Drinktober!
The season of terror begins beneath a Blood Red Sky, with the release of the nightmarish Drinkowe&amp;rsquo;en video trailer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She’s back!! </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/she-s-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/she-s-back/</guid>
      <description>She’s back!!! Due to a short break, mainly consisting of the website not letting me log on, a bout of horrendous flu which killed me completely for a week and my job being ridiculously full on for several days which consumed my life&amp;hellip;.. I am back!!
Just in time for the end to be in sight! Thank you to everyone who has donated so far, this has certainly been a journey to this point 😂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 25 - Pew! Pew!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-25-pew-pew/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-25-pew-pew/</guid>
      <description>Beer and video games - not a bad way to spend the 25th of #Drinktober!
Things take a spooky turn tomorrow as we begin the countdown to Drinkowe&amp;rsquo;en</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 24 - As long as you cleanup after</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-24-as-long-as-you-cleanup-after/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-24-as-long-as-you-cleanup-after/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the 24th of #Drinktober - just one more week to go! Tonight&amp;rsquo;s is another Loch Lomond beer - this one&amp;rsquo;s Come on Pilgrim New England IPA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 23 - Night of the comet</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-23-night-of-the-comet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-23-night-of-the-comet/</guid>
      <description>Oh deer. Tonight&amp;rsquo;s #Drinktober offering is a Comet dry-hopped lager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 22 - High Voltage</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-22-high-voltage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-22-high-voltage/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a real shocker for the 22nd of #Drinktober, as we head to the Electric Cafe, probably for some electric sausage &amp;amp; chips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 21 - Different class</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-21-different-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-21-different-class/</guid>
      <description>21st of #Drinktober, and tonight&amp;rsquo;s beer is a Loch Lomond Different Class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 20 - We all float here</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-20-we-all-float-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-20-we-all-float-here/</guid>
      <description>The strangest thing happened for the 20th of #Drinktober.
Just a couple of sips of my beer and I found myself free from the shackles of gravity and beginning to Levitate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 19 - For those about to Bock</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-19-for-those-about-to-bock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-19-for-those-about-to-bock/</guid>
      <description>Day 19 of #Drinktober comes to you all the way from Bocktoberfest.
Prost!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 18 - Keep taking the Pils</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-18-keep-taking-the-pils/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-18-keep-taking-the-pils/</guid>
      <description>Yep, Vikki was working at Erofame again last week, so I&amp;rsquo;ve got a nice drop of Gilde Pilsener for the 18th of #Drinktober, all the way from Hannover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 17 - Don&#39;cha think?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-17-don-cha-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-17-don-cha-think/</guid>
      <description>#Drinktober the 17th sees me back to normal. Tonight&amp;rsquo;s post might be a little less spectacular but it&amp;rsquo;s still pretty Iconic :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 16 - SMASH!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-16-smash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-16-smash/</guid>
      <description>Disaster strikes on the 16th of #Drinktober, as Gamma Ray exposure unleashes my infinite rage and I&amp;rsquo;m transformed into the Incredible Drunk Hulk, rampaging across the city in search of more beer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 15 - No clever name tonight</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-15-no-clever-name-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-15-no-clever-name-tonight/</guid>
      <description>Crystal wheat beer for the 15th of #Drinktober, with Hop Foundry&amp;rsquo;s Kristallweizen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 14 - Never a frown</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-14-never-a-frown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-14-never-a-frown/</guid>
      <description>14th of #Drinktober and I&amp;rsquo;m just having a normal Monday, sitting around in my Golden Crown as you do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 13 - We&#39;ll get there fast and then we&#39;ll take it slow</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-13-we-ll-get-there-fast-and-then-we-ll-take-it-slow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-13-we-ll-get-there-fast-and-then-we-ll-take-it-slow/</guid>
      <description>After I made it back from the depths of space, I needed a nice holiday.
Here I am, relaxing in a tropical paradise with a can of Kokomo passion fruit and grapefruit pale ale :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>J2hooooooooe</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/j2hooooooooe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/j2hooooooooe/</guid>
      <description>Had a few days off posting due to work and personal life drama so I’m back! Enjoying the J20 life and my new favourite indulgence&amp;hellip;. Black Forest milkshakes. Chocolate milkshake, black cherries, blend it up&amp;hellip;. no wonder I’m not skinny despite the lack of meat!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 12 - Park in it, Viking!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-12-park-in-it-viking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-12-park-in-it-viking/</guid>
      <description>Blasting across time and space for the 12th of #Drinktober, we find the mightiest warrior in the galaxy - the fearsome Space Viking!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 11 - So not the little guys from Fraggle Rock then?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-11-so-not-the-little-guys-from-fraggle-rock-then/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-11-so-not-the-little-guys-from-fraggle-rock-then/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had some very nice beers so far in #Drinktober, but tonight&amp;rsquo;s was a Doozie. From the excellently named By The Horns brewery \m/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Absolute vegan bullshit</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/absolute-vegan-bullshit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/absolute-vegan-bullshit/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever eaten a vegan sausage? I have now. It was awful. Had to spit it out, think it ruined my life.
Three more weeks of this. Vegan sausage bullshit. It’s making me sad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 10 - Is this about fancying the Scarlet Witch?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-10-is-this-about-fancying-the-scarlet-witch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-10-is-this-about-fancying-the-scarlet-witch/</guid>
      <description>10 days into #Drinktober and I&amp;rsquo;ve been overcome with Wanderlust</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef dripping </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/beef-dripping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/beef-dripping/</guid>
      <description>I don’t have anything exciting to say. I’ve just accepted drinking water is my life now&amp;hellip;. made a vegan sausage casserole for tomorrow nights dinner and made very nice dumplings to chuck in. Of course housemate then reminds me that they have beef dripping in, so I can’t have them. Chuffing excellent. Fml.
Over and out 🙄</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharks!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/sharks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/sharks/</guid>
      <description>9th of #Drinktober. I heard it would be a Perfect Storm - I wasn&amp;rsquo;t expecting a Sharknado!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 8 - Curious</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-8-curious/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-8-curious/</guid>
      <description>Getting a little fruity for the 8th of #Drinktober with this orange infused IPA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foam shrimp and tramps shoes. </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/that-was-horrible/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/that-was-horrible/</guid>
      <description>Today I had a late meeting again, so popped to the pub for the ultimate test. I was gaggingggggg for a drink. Any drink. Wine. Gin. Terps. I fancied one.
The batman (I meant barman but autocorrect knows best) recommended an Alcohol Free Kopperberg. “It’s just like the real thing! You can’t even tell the difference!” I was assured. Not a cider drinker but I thought give it a bash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7 - Hat</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-7-hat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-7-hat/</guid>
      <description>Going cowboy style for the 7th of #Drinktober with this Wild Bill&amp;rsquo;s IPA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6 - HONK!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-6-honk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-6-honk/</guid>
      <description>For the 6th of #Drinktober, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d have a nice quite drink in the village. Unluckily for me, my plans were disrupted by the arrival of this Mad Goose!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegetarianism is just a big Miss-Steak</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/is-vegetarian-a-big-miss-steak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/is-vegetarian-a-big-miss-steak/</guid>
      <description>I’ve realised that this site has become more my rambling blog than anything so I’ll keep it brief today! 90’s Carrie Bradshaw narration isn’t a good look for me.
Still alcohol free and I’ve developed a new love for good old water. Managed to stay off the quorn today and had a nice Sunday dinner feat. nut roast. I have however replaced my wine habit with a spending habit: I’ve bought a painting, another lamp, a hat, a magnetic eyelash set, a kaftan, a pigeon pin badge and a gift for the missus already this weekend (the last ones a secret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5 - Du Hast Bier</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-5-du-hast-bier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-5-du-hast-bier/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve got a pussy!
I have a dick-ah!
So what&amp;rsquo;s the problem?
Let&amp;rsquo;s do it quiiiiick
 Pulling out all the stops for the 5th of #Drinktober, for this Rammsteiner Pilsner I actually went on tour with Rammstein and they let me ride their giant cock cannon, as you can see in the totally real and definitely not at all photoshopped picture below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habit is a funny thing </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/habit-is-a-funny-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/habit-is-a-funny-thing/</guid>
      <description>Habits are funny aren’t they! 5 days in and I’ve lost count of the number of times I’ve thought “oh I’ll just grab a coke” or wandered aimlessly to the wine aisle and spent £15 before I’ve even thought about if I actually want it!
Today was chilled with the wife and I’ve smashed in a decent homemade Quorn Lasagne. I now own 48% shares in Quorn FYI. My skin is also looking much brighter, although I do smash a load of acid on my face every night because 30’s, so it could also be that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4 - Friday Night Fever</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-4-friday-night-fever/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-4-friday-night-fever/</guid>
      <description>#Drinktober the 4th and I hit the dance floor to show off my moves with this Disco Forklift Truck.
(The forklift&amp;rsquo;s parked outside, obviously)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get your Friday Heidi on </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/cranberry-craze/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/cranberry-craze/</guid>
      <description>Today is slightly better! Purchased some iron tablets: turned out that’s what fucked me up yesterday. An iron tablet and a multivit and I’m off.
I went out for work drinks this evening and had (drum roll please!) a J20 and a virgin cocktail&amp;hellip;. Which was nice but called ‘the love island’ so minus 3 points. I also spent a hideous amount on experimental quorn and nutroasts in Lidl. I’m currently sipping cranberry juice out of a wine glass so I can express my inner Friday Heidi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3 - Twisted</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-3-twisted/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-3-twisted/</guid>
      <description>For the 3rd of #Drinktober, a poorly executed tribute to the late Keith Flint as I become the twisted FireCatcher!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FML give me a kebab</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/fml-give-me-a-kebab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/fml-give-me-a-kebab/</guid>
      <description>Well today has kicked my arse. I’ve felt absolutely crap all day: not sure if it’s lack of meat or caffeine. Shit day, sat in a meeting until 10.30 surrounded by wine and burgers&amp;hellip;. kill me now. I also had my first Ribena. What a load of shit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2.5 - This is fucking Quorn</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-2-5-this-is-fucking-quorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-2-5-this-is-fucking-quorn/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2 - 5 miles off the ground</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-2-5-miles-off-the-ground/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-2-5-miles-off-the-ground/</guid>
      <description>When we shoot to kill
And you know we always will
It&amp;rsquo;s a bomber! It&amp;rsquo;s a bomber!
 A Lancaster bomber - for the 2nd of #Drinktober I&amp;rsquo;ve got this rather tasty amber ale, even if it is named for the dark lands on the Wrong side of the Pennines&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1.5 - Meanwhile on Planet Heidi</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-1-5-meanwhile-on-planet-heidi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-1-5-meanwhile-on-planet-heidi/</guid>
      <description>kill me now</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1 - Dirt Cheap</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-1-dirt-cheap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2019/day-1-dirt-cheap/</guid>
      <description>Contracts&amp;hellip;
Neckties!
HIGH VOLTAGE!!!
#Drinktober 2019 kicks into action with some Dirty Deeds</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drinktober 2019</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>Drinktober It’s all about raising money for a very good cause – Macmillan Cancer Support.
Macmillan provide physical, financial and emotional support to people with cancer to help them live life as fully as possible. It’s a fantastic charity and the help and support means a lot to many people.
So, for the fourth year in a row, absolute leg-end superstar Heidi is going to pass on the prosecco, say nein to the wine and just giving up any and all alcohol for a gruelling 31 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drinktober 2019</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/donate-pride/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/donate-pride/</guid>
      <description>Donation info: Pride relies on donations to help us put on the best event we possibly can: last year our average donation was less than 1p per attendee :(
You can donate by&amp;hellip;.
  Paypal at: https://prideinhull.co.uk/donate/
  (PayPal donation address is heidi@prideinhull.co.uk)
  Using Amazon Smile and selecting Hull LGBT+ Community Pride as your chosen charity, at no cost to you!
  Texting Text HULL 3 to 70085 to donate £3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 31 - Drinkoween!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-31-drinkoween/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-31-drinkoween/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the 31st of #Drinktober - #Drinkoween!
So there was really no other option than to assemble a bunch of my spookiest stuff and finish off the month with the &amp;ldquo;Unofficial Beer Of Halloween&amp;rdquo; - Hobgoblin!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 30 - Blue moon</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-30-blue-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-30-blue-moon/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the 30th of #Drinktober
After escaping the Medusa&amp;rsquo;s petrifying gaze I thought I was safe, until the rising of the Blue Moon unleashed the beast within - transforming me into the dreaded Blue Wolfman!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 29 - Turned to stone</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-29-turned-to-stone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-29-turned-to-stone/</guid>
      <description>Disaster strikes for the 29th of #Drinktober - I&amp;rsquo;ve been turned into stone by the fearsome Medusa!
Can I break the spell before the next exciting installment? Tune in tomorrow to find out&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 27 - Pumpking</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-27-pumpking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-27-pumpking/</guid>
      <description>A horrifying presence arises for the 27th of #Drinktober - Beware the evil of the Pumpking!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 28 - Ghost Ship</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-28-ghost-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-28-ghost-ship/</guid>
      <description>Shiver me timbers! Legends tell of a lost pirate vessel, cursed to wander the high seas eternally with her terrifying skeleton crew, only appearing on the 28th of #Drinktober to plunder the booty of the living.
Beware the Ghost Ship, me hearties, lest she take ye to Davy Jones&#39; locker!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 26 - Season of the Witch</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-26-season-of-the-witch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-26-season-of-the-witch/</guid>
      <description>Getting close to Halloween now, so for the rest of #Drinktober I&amp;rsquo;ll be drinking the spookiest beers I can find, starting with this Blonde Witch :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 25 - Skål!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-25-sk%C3%A5l/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-25-sk%C3%A5l/</guid>
      <description>A Viking theme for the 25th of #Drinktober with a mighty horn of Jorvik ale. Skål!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 24 - Up the Irons</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-24-up-the-irons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-24-up-the-irons/</guid>
      <description>For the 24th of #Drinktober it&amp;rsquo;s on with the Maiden shirt and up with the horns for a lovely bottle of Trooper \m/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 23 - Urban Fox</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-23-urban-fox/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-23-urban-fox/</guid>
      <description>Slept like crap yesterday and I&amp;rsquo;m absolutely shattered tonight, so no chance of any comical costume shenanigans:(
But it&amp;rsquo;ll take more than that to stop me celebrating the 23rd of #Drinktober with this Urban Fox red ale :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 22 - Proper Job</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-22-proper-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-22-proper-job/</guid>
      <description>22nd of #Drinktober - tonight I&amp;rsquo;m having a Proper Job :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 21 - Rheinbacher</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-21-rheinbacher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-21-rheinbacher/</guid>
      <description>Getting a bit more mileage out of my awesome new beer stein for the 21st of #Drinktober with a Rheinbacher Weissbier and a German shirt I borrowed from Vikki</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 20 - Yarr!!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-20-yarr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-20-yarr/</guid>
      <description>Yarr! Little bit of a nautical theme for the 20th of #Drinktober - Cap&amp;rsquo;n Jonny&amp;rsquo;s relaxing after a long day on the high seas with a Shipyard IPA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 19 - Kingfisher</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-19-kingfisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-19-kingfisher/</guid>
      <description>19th of #Drinktober and it&amp;rsquo;s curry night again. This week I&amp;rsquo;m having a Kingfisher with a lamb naga mirch from the local takeaway :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 18 - Arise, my mighty pink army!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-18-arise-my-mighty-pink-army/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-18-arise-my-mighty-pink-army/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the 18th of #Drinktober and I&amp;rsquo;m having a pint of Joe&amp;rsquo;s Draft ale before going to see the awesome Evil Scarecrow in York \m/
Crabulon! Crabulon! Crabulon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 17 - Bees!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-17-bees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-17-bees/</guid>
      <description>For #Drinktober the 17th I&amp;rsquo;m having a Queen Bee honey ale.
I&amp;rsquo;d be some kind of body-snatched doppelganger if I didn&amp;rsquo;t say that it&amp;rsquo;s the bee&amp;rsquo;s knees and it&amp;rsquo;s given me a bit of a buzz :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 16 - Treacle Treat</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-16-treacle-treat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-16-treacle-treat/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re past the halfway mark now on the 16th of #Drinktober, and I&amp;rsquo;m having a Treacle Treat. Really nice dark ale with a cool skull design, which is always good :)
How&amp;rsquo;s your water/ Heidi? :p</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 15 - Felinfoel ESB</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-15-felinfoel-esb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-15-felinfoel-esb/</guid>
      <description>For the 15th of #Drinktober I&amp;rsquo;m having a Felinfoel ESB, mainly because its got an awesome dragon on the label :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 14 - Dunkel Fester</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-14-dunkel-fester/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-14-dunkel-fester/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the 14th of #Drinktober and I&amp;rsquo;ve got a nice bottle of the excellently named Dunkel Fester :D</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 13 - Time for pudding</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-13-time-for-pudding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-13-time-for-pudding/</guid>
      <description>13th of #Drinktober - tonight I&amp;rsquo;m having a Sticky Toffee Pudding Ale. It&amp;rsquo;s really nice :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 12 - King Cobra</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-12-king-cobra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-12-king-cobra/</guid>
      <description>12th of #Drinktober and it&amp;rsquo;s curry night so I&amp;rsquo;m having a King Cobra. Hail to the King, baby!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 11 - We are the Road Crew</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-11-we-are-the-road-crew/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-11-we-are-the-road-crew/</guid>
      <description>11th of #Drinktober and I&amp;rsquo;m busting out an old favourite - Motörhead Röad Crew \m/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 10 - Dark matters</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-10-dark-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-10-dark-matters/</guid>
      <description>10th of #Drinktober, and tonight I&amp;rsquo;m having a Dark Matter coffee porter. Nice beer, kind of chocolatey ! :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 9 - Oktoberfest</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-9-oktoberfest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-9-oktoberfest/</guid>
      <description>For the 9th of #Drinktober I&amp;rsquo;ve got a great big Stein of Oktoberfest Bier which Vikki brought me back from Germany last week. Prost!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 8 - Hot tub (but no time machine)</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-8-hot-tub-but-no-time-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-8-hot-tub-but-no-time-machine/</guid>
      <description>The 8th of #Drinktober finds me recovering from an awesome weekend of retro gaming by depeopling in the hot tub with this Beardo IPA and season 5 of Steven Universe :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7 - Guinness</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-7-guinness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-7-guinness/</guid>
      <description>Bit of a quiet one for the 7th of #Drinktober, just chilling out with a pint of Guinness after video gaming all weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6 - A Thirst for Justice</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-6-a-thirst-for-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-6-a-thirst-for-justice/</guid>
      <description>For the 6th of #Drinktober, Judge Beerman is quenching his thirst for justice with a pint of Wadworth IPA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5 - Modelo (and a burrito)</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-5-modelo-and-a-burrito/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-5-modelo-and-a-burrito/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m away for the weekend so starting early for the 5th of #Drinktober with a Modelo and a burrito :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4 - Hoptical Illusion</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-4-hoptical-illusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day-4-hoptical-illusion/</guid>
      <description>Strange and mysterious goings on for the 4th of #Drinktober.
Am I really drinking this beer, or is it just a&amp;hellip; Hoptical Illusion&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Dance</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/ghost-dance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/ghost-dance/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the third of #Drinktober, following up last night&amp;rsquo;s cowboy beer with this Ghost Dance Chinook Pale Ale, which is rather nice and hoppy :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jesse James IPA</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day2/</guid>
      <description>Howdy there, pardners! For the second of #Drinktober, a quick raid of Aldi&amp;rsquo;s craft beer section yielded up this cowboy-themed American Pale Ale - seemed only right to dress for the occasion</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drinktober 2018 Begins!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2018/day1/</guid>
      <description>Right then, let&amp;rsquo;s get this show on the road shall we?
#Drinktober 2018 starts off nice and easy with some Heineken that was still in the fridge from the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 31 - Drinkoween!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-31-drinkoween/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-31-drinkoween/</guid>
      <description>Bit of a spooky theme for the 31st of #Drinktober - it&amp;rsquo;s Drinkoween!
Tonight I&amp;rsquo;m drinking Pumpking - evil pumpkin beer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 30 - Cuba libre</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-20-cuba-libre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-20-cuba-libre/</guid>
      <description>30th of #Drinktober - only one more day to go! Cuba Libre tonight, another premixed canned job :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 20 - Roadcrew</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-20-roadcrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-20-roadcrew/</guid>
      <description>20th of #Drinktober, tonight I&amp;rsquo;ve got a pint of Roadcrew \m/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 29 - Tastes like strawberries</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-29-tastes-like-strawberries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-29-tastes-like-strawberries/</guid>
      <description>Not long to go now! 29th of #Drinktober, tonight&amp;rsquo;s offering is a strawberry daiquiri. Learned my lesson from the Pina colada and beefed it up with a drop of Bacardi :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 28 - A bit of DnB</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-28-a-bit-of-dnb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-28-a-bit-of-dnb/</guid>
      <description>28th of #Drinktober, and tonight I&amp;rsquo;ve found this alcoholic dandelion &amp;amp; burdock. It&amp;rsquo;s not bad :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 27 - Tell &#39;em about the honey, Mummy!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-28-tell-em-about-the-honey-mummy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-28-tell-em-about-the-honey-mummy/</guid>
      <description>27th of #Drinktober, tonight I had a honey Jack Daniel&amp;rsquo;s &amp;amp; lemonade while I was out being crafty in the garage
__</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 26 - Pimms</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/26-pimms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/26-pimms/</guid>
      <description>For the 26th of #Drinktober, I finally opened this can of Pimms with blackberry and elderflower that&amp;rsquo;s been lurking in the fridge for a couple of years now. I&amp;rsquo;m not entirely sure what Pimms is exactly, but this basically tastes like Ribena.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 25 - This wasn&#39;t my best idea</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-25-this-wasn-t-my-best-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-25-this-wasn-t-my-best-idea/</guid>
      <description>25th of #Drinktober, and tonight&amp;rsquo;s theme is &amp;ldquo;wow, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a lot of tequila left. I wonder if it mixes well with this tropical fruit drink?&amp;rdquo;
Narrator : It did not mix well</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 24 - Getting caught in the rain</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-24-getting-caught-in-the-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-24-getting-caught-in-the-rain/</guid>
      <description>24th of #Drinktober - tonight I&amp;rsquo;ve got some kind of ready-mixed pina colada I found at Sainsbury&amp;rsquo;s. Very tropical</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 23 - Ouzo margarita</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-23-ouzo-margarita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-23-ouzo-margarita/</guid>
      <description>23rd of #Drinktober - random concoction week continues with this Ouzo margarita. It kind of works :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 22 - What even is this stuff?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-22-what-even-is-this-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-22-what-even-is-this-stuff/</guid>
      <description>22nd of #Drinktober, and we&amp;rsquo;ve reached the &amp;ldquo;any old shite that&amp;rsquo;s in the house&amp;rdquo; stage ) This is from a box of pre-packaged &amp;ldquo;flavoured shots&amp;rdquo; - think this was the apple one.
__</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 21 - TVR</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-21-tvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-21-tvr/</guid>
      <description>Back on a more normal schedule for the 21st of #Drinktober and tonight is a total student classic, the TVR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 19 - Frankenstein creation</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-19-frankenstein-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-19-frankenstein-creation/</guid>
      <description>19th of #Drinktober and I&amp;rsquo;m getting inventive tonight. I call this one the Mead-garita. Half margarita mix, half mead - it&amp;rsquo;s actually pretty good :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 18 - No sleep...</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-18-no-sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-18-no-sleep/</guid>
      <description>18th of #Drinktober - Brooklyn Lager tonight</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 17 - Cactus Jack</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-17-cactus-jack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-17-cactus-jack/</guid>
      <description>17th of #Drinktober, and tonight it&amp;rsquo;s Cactus Jack&amp;rsquo;s Blackjack flavour schnapps. You probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t like this one either :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 16 - Ouzo</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-16-ouzo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-16-ouzo/</guid>
      <description>Ouzo and lemonade tonight for the 16th of #Drinktober - we&amp;rsquo;re past the halfway mark now, how&amp;rsquo;s your resolve holding up? :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 15 - Random</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-15-random/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-15-random/</guid>
      <description>15th of #Drinktober and today I&amp;rsquo;m drinking some random stuff I found at Aldi. &amp;ldquo;Alizé&amp;rdquo;, apparently - mix of cognac, vodka and passion fruit. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know French vodka was a thing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 14 - Scuttle left!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-14-scuttle-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-14-scuttle-left/</guid>
      <description>Alcoholic ginger beer for the 14th of #Drinktober.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 13 - Heineken</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-13-heineken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-13-heineken/</guid>
      <description>Out of town and such with the shockingly expensive and limited hotel bar selection for the 13th of #Drinktober, so it&amp;rsquo;s just a boring old pint of Heineken this evening. Might have to go find a proper pub&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 12 - More gin!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-12-more-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-12-more-gin/</guid>
      <description>#Drinktober the 12th. Gin and pink grapefruit tonight - it&amp;rsquo;s really rather nice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 11 - Onwards to Valhalla!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-11-onwards-to-valhalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-11-onwards-to-valhalla/</guid>
      <description>11th of #Drinktober and I&amp;rsquo;ve gone all Viking with a horn of mead \m/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 10 - Tequila time!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-10-tequila-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-10-tequila-time/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the 10th of #Drinktober and tonight I&amp;rsquo;m having a margarita</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 9 - bubbles!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-9-bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-9-bubbles/</guid>
      <description>Drop of cava for the 9th of #Drinktober - bubbleicious!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 8 - Sunshine!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-8-sunshine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-8-sunshine/</guid>
      <description>8th of #Drinktober and just for a change the daystar showed its face. Seemed like a good opportunity to take this Malibu &amp;amp; pineapple out in the garden and catch a bit of sun</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7 - This one&#39;s for Lemmy</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-7-this-one-s-for-lemmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-7-this-one-s-for-lemmy/</guid>
      <description>Jack and coke for the 7th of #Drinktober. This one&amp;rsquo;s dedicated to Lemmy \m/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6 - Curry night!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-6-curry-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-6-curry-night/</guid>
      <description>6th of #Drinktober, and it&amp;rsquo;s Curry night! So that means chicken vindaloo and frosty Indian lager :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5 - Vodka and coke</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-5-vodka-and-coke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-5-vodka-and-coke/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the 5th of #Drinktober, and today I&amp;rsquo;m having vodka and coke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4 - Old Rosie</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-4-old-rosie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-4-old-rosie/</guid>
      <description>Drop of cider for the 4th of #Drinktober - cheers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3 - Scurvy</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-3-scurvy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-3-scurvy/</guid>
      <description>For the 3rd of #Drinktober, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a bit of a pirate theme going, with Captain Morgan and coke. Yarr!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2 - Gin o&#39;Clock</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-2-gin-o-clock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-2-gin-o-clock/</guid>
      <description>2nd of #Drinktober. Gin o&amp;rsquo;Clock :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1 - It begins!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-1-it-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2017/day-1-it-begins/</guid>
      <description>#Drinktober begins with a nice pint of fine Ruby ale. Mmm, lovely&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/privacy/</guid>
      <description>PRIVACY NOTICE Last updated September 19, 2020
Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at Drinktober (&amp;ldquo;Company&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy notice, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at drinktober@technicalhat.com.
When you visit our website https://drinktober.co.uk/ (the &amp;ldquo;Website&amp;rdquo;), and more generally, use any of our services (the &amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo;, which include the Website), we appreciate that you are trusting us with your personal information.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
