<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drinktober 2020</title>
    <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Drinktober 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Do you like movies about gladiators?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/do-you-like-movies-about-gladiators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/do-you-like-movies-about-gladiators/</guid>
      <description>My name is Citrus Maxima. Commander of the armies of the Hops. General of the zesty Legions, loyal servant of the brew Emperor. Drinker of a finished pint, holder of an empty glass. And I will have my beer, in this pub or the next!
 Stepping back in time for the 10th of Drinktober, to the days of Ancient Rome, where the mighty gladiator Citrus Maxima conquered the arena and toppled an empire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ich habe Space Dementia</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/ich-habe-space-dementia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/ich-habe-space-dementia/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s that there? I don&amp;rsquo;t care
Sat alone, with no cards, playing solitaire
Breathe cold air, fuel&amp;rsquo;s spent yeah
Ich habe space dementia
Space Dementia, Evil Scarecrow
 I&amp;rsquo;ve been blasted into the deep space for the 9th of Drinktober, courtesy of Arbor Ales&#39; Space Hardware.
I think the isolation has sent me a bit funny - am I really seeing Neville the space hedgehog or has my mind succumbed to Space Dementia?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All cracked up</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/all-cracked-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/all-cracked-up/</guid>
      <description>This wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite what I meant by a night on the tiles!
For the 8th of Drinktober, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a nice big can of Mosaic ale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All washed up</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/all-washed-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/all-washed-up/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been attacked by sea monsters, and hurled into the deep by an ungrateful crew, but at last, my nautical adventure comes to a happy ending, as I&amp;rsquo;ve washed up on this Tropical island.
Now to enjoy a few tasty beers among the palm trees with my little parrot buddy Iago.
Cheers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutiny!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/mutiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/mutiny/</guid>
      <description>Gather round and listen to this tale of treachery upon the high seas.
It seems my shipmates took offence to my language yesterday, in the middle of the night those mutinous dogs dragged me from my bunk and tossed me overboard.
I managed to save myself from Davey Jones&#39; locker by lashing a raft together from some driftwood, but now I&amp;rsquo;m a castaway, adrift upon the Big Sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>With a what now?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/with-a-what-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/with-a-what-now/</guid>
      <description>Fuck! You! You&amp;rsquo;re a fucking wanker! We&amp;rsquo;re gonna punch you right in the balls!
Fuck! You! With a fucking anchor! You&amp;rsquo;re all cunts so fuck you all!
Alestorm - Fucked with an anchor
 Stretching the theme a little bit for the 5th of Drinktober, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist the opportunity to combine three of my favourite things. Pirate costumes, heavy metal and gratuitous swearing!
Sing along, ye scurvy dogs!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to get Loco!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/it-s-time-to-get-loco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/it-s-time-to-get-loco/</guid>
      <description>For the 4th of Drinktober we step into the ring with the mighty El Loco - the most feared luchador in all of East Yorkshire!
Undefeated in every match, this fearsome hero of the ring strikes terror into the hearts of his opponents, and loves nothing more than to celebrate a successful match with a victory beer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water leaks from the ceiling and you also have to drink it </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/water-leaks-from-the-ceiling-and-you-have-to-drink-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/water-leaks-from-the-ceiling-and-you-have-to-drink-it/</guid>
      <description>Ok day three, whatcha got?
Well we all know I’m a prolific stress drinker. So today I had a small paddy that my house is essentially falling down, nothing works and my pipes (Which are leaking) are made of lead (apparently this is bad). So I realllllly fancied some wine, or 9 double vodkas of something .
However, I’ve stayed strong and drank water all goddamn day. Which is slightly less appealing to drink when it’s slowly dripping from your ceiling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a lovely day!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/what-a-lovely-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/what-a-lovely-day/</guid>
      <description>Beer. Beer never changes.
When the old world fell, only a few survived. Roaming the blacktop between the remnants of the cities, scavenging for the last remaining booze of a lost civilisation.
A drop of ale in the wasteland can help keep a man sane - because if you don&amp;rsquo;t keep your head&amp;hellip; you&amp;rsquo;re nothing but Roadkill&amp;hellip;
 Things are going a little bit post-apocalyptic for the 3rd of Drinktober as I take to the roads of the blasted wasteland that was once Yorkshire in search of more beer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking a little pale</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/looking-a-little-pale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/looking-a-little-pale/</guid>
      <description>A fairly quiet one for the second of Drinktober. I&amp;rsquo;m hard at work in the Beercave prepping for the insanity to come, just taking a break to enjoy a tasty Rudgate Pale.
Tune in tomorrow, same beer time, same beer channel, when we start to kick things up a notch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAY 2! </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2, feeling confident! Day one was a piece of piss because I was ill, so I slept through my normal drinking time! So far today I’m on 5 coffees, a herbal tea and 4 waters, might be piddling for England but sober af! 🙌🏻</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back once again with the Drunken Master</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/back-once-again-with-the-drunken-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/back-once-again-with-the-drunken-master/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first of Drinktober, and I should be working hard on getting everything set up for this year&amp;rsquo;s shenanigans, but instead here I am just chilling in my hammock with a nice cold lager.
I guess I&amp;rsquo;m just a Lazy Boy ;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drinktober 2020 Trailer</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/drinktober-2020-trailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/drinktober-2020-trailer/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the official video trailer for Drinktober 2020. Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drinktober 2020 - Lockdown lock-in!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/drinktober-2020-lockdown-lock-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2020/drinktober-2020-lockdown-lock-in/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to Drinktober 2020 - we&amp;rsquo;re having a lock-in! Or a lockdown! Hopefully not getting locked up&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;m not the type to let a little thing like a global pandemic, or impending political and economic collapse get in the way of a good time, so Drinktober 2020 is going ahead as scheduled.
I&amp;rsquo;ve got an exciting range of beers lined up thanks to the excellent chaps at Beer Bandits, conveniently located just down the road from me, and lots of extremely silly antics planned, so watch this space and ready your wallets for the biggest Drinktober yet!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
