<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drinktober 2021</title>
    <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Drinktober 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Twisted</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/twisted/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/twisted/</guid>
      <description>VII: Me, absolutely twisted, coming home with three swords.
IX: Me, waking up the next morning in a room with three swords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you want beef then bring the ruckus</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/if-you-want-beef-then-bring-the-ruckus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/if-you-want-beef-then-bring-the-ruckus/</guid>
      <description>Another top act added to the bill for the Drinktober 2021 fundraising gig!
Bringing fresh C.R.E.A.M. from the dairies of Shaolin, these legendary bovine hip hop superstars ain&amp;rsquo;t nuthin to fuck wit. It&amp;rsquo;s the mighty Moo Tang Clan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONSUME</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/consume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/consume/</guid>
      <description>Aliens beware, I&amp;rsquo;m here to drink beer and kick ass - and I&amp;rsquo;ve nearly finished my beer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pompatus</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pompatus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pompatus/</guid>
      <description>Some people call me the Space Cowboy.
Some call me the Gangster of Love
But most people call me Jonny, because that&amp;rsquo;s like, my name, you know?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horsin&#39; Around</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/horsin-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/horsin-around/</guid>
      <description>Hitting the gym tonight and I&amp;rsquo;ve found the perfect recovery drink.
When you want to keep your workout stable, you can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with a little extra Horse Power!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whatever a spider can</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/whatever-a-spider-can/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/whatever-a-spider-can/</guid>
      <description>Today I&amp;rsquo;ve just been hanging out in my cool new black Spider suit which I&amp;rsquo;m sure isn&amp;rsquo;t secretly evil or anything! Here&amp;rsquo;s hoping I don&amp;rsquo;t find myself caught up in its Dark Web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master of Beasts</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/master-of-beasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/master-of-beasts/</guid>
      <description>A mighty warrior approaches for today&amp;rsquo;s Drinktober.
Riding through the wilderness atop Maui, his fearsome battle hedgehog comes the mighty Beast Master. This unstoppable barbarian hero lives only for vengeance - and beer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pump it up a little more</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pump-it-up-a-little-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pump-it-up-a-little-more/</guid>
      <description>Lock up your pantries!
That rascally rogue Jam Master Jonny is on the loose again, roaming across town with his bicycle pump. No fruity preserve is safe from his deranged mission to Pump Up The Jam!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarr</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/yarr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/yarr/</guid>
      <description>Arr, it be a tough life on the seven seas, sometimes when the looting and plundering hits a quiet spell it can be hard for a cap&amp;rsquo;n to keep up with all his streaming subscriptions.
If ye don&amp;rsquo;t want yer crew to mutiny on account of not being able to get Disney+ ye might have to sail the dangerous waters of the Pirate Bay&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Chopper</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/big-chopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/big-chopper/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m taking a break from it all in my cabin in the woods, but would you believe it? The ring pulls on all the beer I brought with me have snapped off, leaving me unable to open them!!
Luckily I came prepared - I just need to introduce the cans to my Axe Edge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even more pew!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/even-more-pew/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/even-more-pew/</guid>
      <description>If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing we love here at Drinktober, it&amp;rsquo;s shamelessly reusing the same prop twice and calling it a storyline :)
I thought I&amp;rsquo;d finally fought off the invaders, but this last one turned out to be too much for me to handle.
Now my only chance to survive is if I can Escape the Mothership!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pew! Pew!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pew-pew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/pew-pew/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been overrun by Space Invaders!
Luckily I&amp;rsquo;ve got my trusty laser rifle at hand but they just keep on coming, Wave After Wave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t panic! At the Disco</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/don-t-panic-at-the-disco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/don-t-panic-at-the-disco/</guid>
      <description>It may be Sunday but here at Drinktober towers we&amp;rsquo;re still feeling the Saturday Night Fever.
Time to bust out the shiny balls and hit the floor to some tasty beats from the Disco King!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelations and Carvery  </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/revelations-and-carvery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/revelations-and-carvery/</guid>
      <description>Another day, more water and Heineken Zero! I also appear to have replaced vino with food considering the amount of carvery I’ve put away today.
I&amp;rsquo;ve had a weekend of sleep, reading and revelations being by myself and sober. Some of my closer people know this has been a bit of a mad year for me with a lot of anxiety and change, but apparently it appears that I actually quite enjoy being by myself and I don’t need anyone to meet my needs or look after me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Born in the Moo S E</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/born-in-the-moo-s-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/born-in-the-moo-s-e/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve attracted some top talent for this year&amp;rsquo;s Drinktober!
Book your tickets now for our epic fundraising concert, featuring top hits like &amp;ldquo;Born to Ruminate&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Antlers in the Dark&amp;rdquo;, by the mighty, the majestic, the magnificent : Moose Springsteen!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not yet a Cat-astrophe 🐈‍⬛ </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/not-yet-a-ca-tastrophe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/not-yet-a-ca-tastrophe/</guid>
      <description>Day 2! 💪
Fiyero (AKA Mr Fifi) is enthralled by this new beer which doesnt make mother fall over.
A day of crazy pirate mini golfing was cancelled due to me a) still being sick af and b) the usual rain of the North. So instead of hitting the pub with my homies, I have scrubbed a floor, eaten lasagne with my neighbours, eaten the worlds hottest noodles (TM) and stayed off the booze!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beers don&#39;t hit back</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/beers-don-t-hit-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/beers-don-t-hit-back/</guid>
      <description>And we&amp;rsquo;re off! Welcome back to another month of the booze-inspired mayhem known as Drinktober. We&amp;rsquo;ve got some absolutely phenomenal stuff coming up this year so get ready to go hammer on that donate button!
Kicking things off with a kung fu classic as I whip out my trusty beer-chucks and prepare to Enter the Dragon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Zero to Hero (ish)!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/from-zero-to-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/from-zero-to-hero/</guid>
      <description>Look at that artistic photo! The colour, the style, the Asthetic! 📸
Some of you might know this has been a bit of a mad year for me, certainly not one I was expecting, and one I have certainly hit the bar amongst other things pretty bloody hard. So this year will probably be my biggest challenge yet.
Kicking it off today is this flirty little Heineken 0.0 delight, served with a bloody amazing steak sandwich at my favourite establishment The Punch Hotel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep taking the pils </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/keep-taking-the-pils/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2021/keep-taking-the-pils/</guid>
      <description>Droogies, boozers, strumpets and losers! Welcome once more to the booziest charity event of the year : Drinktober!
It&amp;rsquo;s been a loooooong year, but we&amp;rsquo;ve made it this far and it&amp;rsquo;s time to have some fun (well, it&amp;rsquo;s time for me to have some fun. Poor Heidi gets to spend a month on the wagon while I muck about and have a laugh.)
This year we&amp;rsquo;re going even bigger and even better, with more beers, sillier antics, and a bumper crop of poor-quality cosplay, so watch this space and get ready to chuck some cash in the pot and make all this nonsense worthwhile!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
