<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drinktober 2022</title>
    <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Drinktober 2022</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let’s all live in ham-ony</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/let-s-all-live-in-ham-ony/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/let-s-all-live-in-ham-ony/</guid>
      <description>Ordinarily I would be full of wine about now and shouting at the TV, but after a lazy napping day, all I’ve done is drink water (I’m now so hydrated I am part dolphin) and make this fantastic roast.
Yesterday myself and the esteemed Jonathan had some fun and high jinx, with some images that will blow your mind! Plans are already underway for next year…..
Don’t forget that behind all Johnnys hard work, incredible costume wizardry and my sobriety, this is all for an excellent cause: supporting Macmillan who were very supportive in my cousins cancer victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does whatever an iron can</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/does-whatever-an-iron-can/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/does-whatever-an-iron-can/</guid>
      <description>Tonight we have a visit from Yorkshire&amp;rsquo;s mightiest hero. Proud leader of the Northern Avengers!
The unstoppable&amp;hellip;
Iron Bloke!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beeriouser and beeriouser</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/beeriouser-and-beeriouser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/beeriouser-and-beeriouser/</guid>
      <description>Well it&amp;rsquo;s been a strange day.
After seeing this weird white rabbit in a waistcoat out in the bottom field I followed him down a hole and now I&amp;rsquo;m trapped in a strange psychedelic land with no way home.
Still, at least I&amp;rsquo;ve found something to drink!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lettuce Pray 🙏 </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/lettuce-pray/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/lettuce-pray/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to Fridays edition of #whatidowithoutthepub. What did I do without the pub? Well, er…. I went to work, had my covid and flu boosters, ate Moroccan food… nothing very exciting really!
So let’s talk politics: specifically the Daily Star race between a wet lettuce and our recently departed PM (I’ve literally had longer drinking sessions than her term).
I’ve always loved the lettuce 🥬 so of course, it has my backing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joss Ackland&#39;s Spunky Backpack</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/joss-ackland-s-spunky-backpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/joss-ackland-s-spunky-backpack/</guid>
      <description>This is cake - it&amp;rsquo;s a made up drug. It&amp;rsquo;s made of from chemicals by&amp;hellip; sick bastards!
We all like to party, yeah? But only the fool would say &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll enter the nightmare of Cake!&amp;rdquo;
Use your cheese box and say no to metabisturbile amphetamoids!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape from Brew York</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/escape-from-brew-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/escape-from-brew-york/</guid>
      <description>The year is 2023. As society collapses, the walled city of York becomes a futuristic prison. When terrorists hijack a truck full of beer and crash it through the city walls, only one man is tough enough to go in after it.
Kirsch Russel is Snake Beerman in: Escape from Brew York</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do you call a reluctant potato? A hesitater.</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/what-do-you-call-a-reluctant-potato-a-hesitater/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/what-do-you-call-a-reluctant-potato-a-hesitater/</guid>
      <description>What do you call a reluctant potato? A hesitater.
I would likely have a small tipple after a late night at work with very little hesitation usually. However, it’s still #drinktober so alternatives must be found. In todays #whatidowithoutthepub, the only solution seemed to be cooking a shed load of food. Steamed salmon, stuffed sweet potatoes the lot in fact.
Sooner or tater I can can return to the pub, but for now this was pretty s-mash-ing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murder One</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/murder-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/murder-one/</guid>
      <description>Chazz : Who&amp;rsquo;d win in a wrestling match, Lemmy or God?
Chris Moore : Lemmy.
[Rex imitates a game show buzzer]
Chris Moore : &amp;hellip; God?
Rex : Wrong, dickhead, trick question. Lemmy IS God.
-Airheads (1994)
 Today on Drinktober we pay tribute to the Man himself, hard rocking, hard drinking legend Lemmy Kilmister, the unstoppable force behind the greatest band of all time : Motörhead!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Very metal</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/very-metal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/very-metal/</guid>
      <description>+++ SnidertronOs:v4000 Core AI module +++ function HandleRequest(request){ if (request === &#39;Turn it down&#39; || request === &#39;Not to play&#39;){ Say(&#39;No! No no no!&#39;); } IWant = &#39;Rock!&#39;; } function TakeIt(){ throw new Exception(&#39;No! We ain&#39;t gonna take it!&#39;); } A very special guest star for tonight&amp;rsquo;s Drinktober. You can&amp;rsquo;t get much more metal than the D33 Snidertron of robo-metal band Twisted Transistor. He&amp;rsquo;s literally made of the stuff!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheelie Fancied a Beverage </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/wheelie-fancied-a-beverage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/wheelie-fancied-a-beverage/</guid>
      <description>Today I VERY MUCH fancied a little beveragéo….. like I could have happily murdered for a small pint of wine. Still, todays #whatidowithoutthepub I decided to be productive so I cooked some Asian food, cleaned, and did my first ever 5km on an exercise bike.
I mean it’s not exactly a marathon but I’m wheelie pleased with myself, I’ve even supplemented cranberry juice in a wine glass. Who even am I?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellente!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/excellente/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/excellente/</guid>
      <description>The ambeersador&amp;rsquo;s reception is well known throughout Society for the host&amp;rsquo;s exquisite drinks selection, and with this Ferrero Rocher stout he&amp;rsquo;s really spoiling us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A blonde walks (not) into a bar </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/a-blonde-walks-not-into-a-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/a-blonde-walks-not-into-a-bar/</guid>
      <description>I wish I could walk into a bar like, but in todays edition of #whatidowithoutthepub, I decided to take a nice leisurely long stroll to forget about how much I like wine.
Followed by a fairly good steak dinner, I wasn’t thinking about the end of October (which is a mere 15 days, 2 hours and 1 minute away) at all. Honest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beerpocalypse now!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/beerpocalypse-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/beerpocalypse-now/</guid>
      <description>Beer. Beer never changes.
It&amp;rsquo;s the end of the world as we know it, but luckily for me the Vault is well stocked with cans, and if there&amp;rsquo;s one thing that&amp;rsquo;s never in short supply around here it&amp;rsquo;s bottle caps!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biscotti with the boss</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/biscotti-with-the-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/biscotti-with-the-boss/</guid>
      <description>Star Wars week comes to it&amp;rsquo;s thrilling conclusion with this rarely seen side of Death Star life.
Life in the Empire isn&amp;rsquo;t all about blowing up planets and subjugating Rebel scum. Sometimes you need to wind down and take a minute for an Imperial Biscotti Break</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What kind of car takes you to a jedi?  A toyoda. </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/what-kind-of-car-takes-you-to-a-jedi-a-toyoda./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/what-kind-of-car-takes-you-to-a-jedi-a-toyoda./</guid>
      <description>Now wait one minute…. Why does Johnny get to have both all the beers and all the dressing up fun?!!
Todays edition of #whatidowithoutthepub seemed a little boring once again, I’ve done lots of work and housing today but not many sober adventures aside from Asda pharmacy. So please witness this #drinktober Princess Leia special for your viewing pleasure.
Star Wars aside, don’t forget to use the force to dig deep and donate to this important cause for Macmillan Cancer here: https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Saga Continues</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/the-saga-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/the-saga-continues/</guid>
      <description>Continuing with Star Wars week, and Jedi Pastry Master Obi Wan Cannoli has been summoned before the Jedi Council.
They&amp;rsquo;re all really excited to see his Jedi Pie Trick</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice little tee </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/nice-little-tee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/nice-little-tee/</guid>
      <description>Well going back to my realisation of how old I am…. I have once again been to golf practice. 36 cheeky holes, one bad game and a nice sober infused bottle of water with it.
That’s it, that’s the whole post 🫠</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear of the dark (side)</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/fear-of-the-dark-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/fear-of-the-dark-side/</guid>
      <description>You take my life but I&amp;rsquo;ll take yours too
I fire my blaster but I can&amp;rsquo;t hit you
 Star Wars week continues with this little homage to the mighty Iron Maiden!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sobriety is not in my vodkabulary </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/sobriety-is-not-in-my-vodkabulary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/sobriety-is-not-in-my-vodkabulary/</guid>
      <description>Right it’s getting a bit harder now. I’m past the smug ‘look I am a picture of health aren’t I saintly, it’s for charity you know’ stage now and I would like several vinos. I also didn’t get chance to post again yesterday because I worked until chuff o’clock and promptly fell asleep on my furry child so apologies, please forgive me dear readers.
I’m not sure when it happened but I think I have become old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello there</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/hello-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/hello-there/</guid>
      <description>Come in, youg padawan. Enjoy one of my delicious Italian pastries!
Obi Wan Cannoli? Now that&amp;rsquo;s a name I haven&amp;rsquo;t heard in a long time&amp;hellip;
Well of course I know him - he&amp;rsquo;s me!
 It&amp;rsquo;s Star Wars Week* here at Drinktober Towers and we&amp;rsquo;re starting off with a visit to everyone&amp;rsquo;s favourite Jedi Pastry Master, _Obi Wan Cannoli_
* Technically, I&amp;rsquo;ve only got 4 days of SW content, but Star Wars week sounds better :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ragna-rocking out!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/ragna-rocking-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/ragna-rocking-out/</guid>
      <description>Grab your horns and hit the beach, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a Viking Hula party!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s nacho beer</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-nacho-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-nacho-beer/</guid>
      <description>Well apparently when I’m sober I get tired like a regular person, hence I fell asleep at 9pm last night on the sofa 🤦🏼‍♀️
Today I am once again hopped up on water and black coffee, and #whatidowithoutthepub turns out to be work all day. However, to cheer my sober self up Let’s take a moment to appreciate my ridiculous homemade tortilla nachos which I think we can all agree are fairly impressive!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beerman! What is best in life?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/beerman-what-is-best-in-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/beerman-what-is-best-in-life/</guid>
      <description> To crush your empties
See them driven away by the recycling truck
And to hear the opening of a fresh can!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She’s back! </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/she-s-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/she-s-back/</guid>
      <description>I’m alive! And much less snotty!! i also forgot to post yesterday because I am le imbecilé.
This weekend edition of #whatidowithoutthepub includes decorating a table (yes, I’m THAT homosexual I decorated the table, see what you have done to me), responding to the incessant letters we seem to get from local religious groups and moving furniture for my adopted Mum. I also did a nice movie in bed evening with the boy and the cat, which was wholesome af as you can imagine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half man. Half machine. All bargain hunter</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/half-man.half-machine.all-bargain-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/half-man.half-machine.all-bargain-hunter/</guid>
      <description>Dead or alive, you&amp;rsquo;re coming shopping.
It&amp;rsquo;s a tough life being a cyborg cop. When you get done with a hard day of cleaning up the mean streets of Old Detroit, there&amp;rsquo;s still the grocery shopping to be done.
And with that comes the irresistible lure of the SpecialBuys aisle. A chainsaw? A canoe? A complete box set of WWII documentaries?
I&amp;rsquo;d buy that for a dollar!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting cosmic</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/getting-cosmic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/getting-cosmic/</guid>
      <description>A mysterious figure has been spotted in the skies! Flying through the atmosphere, wielding the Power Cosmic!
Behold the mighty Silver Drinker! Herald of Galactus: the devourer of worlds!
Herald of change and disruption!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Snot as bad </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-snot-as-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-snot-as-bad/</guid>
      <description>The good news is I’m past the snot stage and onto the vomit stage! The bad news is that has left little room for comedic #whatidowithoutthepub activities, but hopefully adventures will soon resume now I can successfully roll out of bed and to the sofa.
Today’s tipple is a feisty little cranberry juice, which is actually quite nice, with a lemsip chaser. Would be extra nice with a little vodka in there but here we all are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s only a model!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-only-a-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-only-a-model/</guid>
      <description>At long last, this epic quest has finally come to an end.
I&amp;rsquo;ve followed the mysterious red line around the map, accompanied by inspiring orchestral music, for many years but now in this cave I&amp;rsquo;ve finally found the Holy Grail!
Surely this is the cup of a coder!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down with the sickness </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/down-with-the-sickness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/down-with-the-sickness/</guid>
      <description>I am down with the sickness, like the disturbed sang.
Sadly, considering I fell asleep last night and woke up at 4.30 pm today (and I’m still in bed dying now), I don’t have any comedic #whatidowithoutthepub adventures to share, because I’ve just been sleeping and sick! On the plus I’ve caught up on some reading and some crap bed TV, and I’m far too ill to go to the off license or open the door to londis delivery, so I am still very much sober.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping up with the Joneses</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/keeping-up-with-the-joneses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/keeping-up-with-the-joneses/</guid>
      <description>An archaeological theme for the 6th of Drinktober as Indiana Stout delves back into the hidden mysteries of the past to uncover the secrets of the Last Brewsade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everybody is Kung-Flu fighting </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/everybody-is-kung-flu-fighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/everybody-is-kung-flu-fighting/</guid>
      <description>Good news!!! I am sober and I do not fancy a drink AT ALL!!
Bad news this is primarily due to the fact I have some sort of hideous illness, currently downing lemsip as if it’s Sauvignon Blanc and dying in bed. The cats covered in snot, I coughed so hard the Alexa asked if I was ok, and my nose is as red as a walruses nutsack.
As I die quietly in bed, sober and poorly, remember to donate to an excellent cause and if you can’t donate, can somebody please make me some sort of soup and offer a rendition of soft kitty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You guava be kidding me</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/you-guava-be-kidding-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/you-guava-be-kidding-me/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re barely into the first week of Drinktober when disaster strikes.
I was planning to burn off the calories from all these beers in the gym, but somehow I&amp;rsquo;ve found myself trapped inside this insane game show.
I need to find a way to escape, but the floor is guava!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lettuce begin</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/lettuce-begin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/lettuce-begin/</guid>
      <description>After a very busy, somewhat stressful and full of flu day, ordinarily this is prime circumstances for a nice chianti and a caramel cup.
However, being a good girl observing #whatidowithoutthepub, I decided to cook a nice chicken and Caesar salad and have a vitamin water followed by a terrible film. Sadly I failed to take an appropriate photo so please enjoy the artists impression of me cooking. I also fixed the washing machine so overall sober me is a complete champ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>By Daisies Be Driven</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/by-daisies-be-driven/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/by-daisies-be-driven/</guid>
      <description>Dammit, Plantera, this beer is warm! Go get me another one!
Shocking scenes for the Fourth of Drinktober! Things are turning Fuchsia-ing Hostile as we bear witness to this Vulgar Display of Flower!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just hear meowt</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/just-hear-meowt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/just-hear-meowt/</guid>
      <description>Day three and I’m sat it’s not Cat-utday still. Or at least Friday night when I could enjoy a sweet, sweet vino.
Today was a very busy day which involved much running about and not much time to miss the pub. However, now I’m home alone, this is prime drink o’clock.
Of course, I had to distract myself and find something to fit in with #whatidowithoutthepub so I decided the only healthy thing to do was to dress up my cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheese</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/cheese/</guid>
      <description>Cheese!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I like big putts and I cannot lie</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/i-like-big-putts-and-i-cannot-lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/i-like-big-putts-and-i-cannot-lie/</guid>
      <description>I do enjoy a big putt, although this gives a different meaning to clubbing.
In today’s edition of #whatidowithoutthepub, I very much fancied some day drinking. Possibly left Over lesbian rage. However, it’s for charity innit so I decided to distract myself with my favourite competition sport, Mini Golf.
Although it’s not as fun as drunk mini golf, I did win in a spectacular fashion and looked cute doing so, so I’ll take that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaze into the beer of Dredd!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/gaze-into-the-beer-of-dredd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/gaze-into-the-beer-of-dredd/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been around since the early days you might have noticed I&amp;rsquo;m a bit of a Judge Dredd fanboy.
So when Northern Monk released a Thought Bubble Festival collaboration beer late last year with Jock, one of my favourite Dredd artists, you can be sure I snapped up a few cans quicker than you can say &amp;ldquo;I AM THE LAW!&amp;rdquo;, and couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist hanging on to one to give me a chance to break out the Judge Beerman outfit again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s here!!!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-here/</guid>
      <description>It’s here!!!! Day #1 of the glorious return of everyone’s favourite activity #drinktober
Whilst Johnny has a lovely beer, I’ve undertaken my first instalment of #whatidowithoutthepub, drinking copious Heineken Zeros at a very angry, excellent lesbian energy gig.
Side note, if you’ve never heard Bizarre Fae or Delilah Bon you absolutely should. - Heidi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s gonna be a long, long month</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-gonna-be-a-long-long-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-gonna-be-a-long-long-month/</guid>
      <description>And so it begins!
We&amp;rsquo;re literally blasting off into Drinktober as we answer the question literally nobody was asking: what if the Rocket Man was the Rocketeer?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello? Is this thing on?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/hello-is-this-thing-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/hello-is-this-thing-on/</guid>
      <description>Hey all! Your friendly neighbourhood Beerman here, just kicking the tires and making sure the website&amp;rsquo;s ready to roll for another month of my booze-fuelled shenanigans!
While you&amp;rsquo;re here, why not check out the sneaky preview of some of the things to look forward to in what&amp;rsquo;s promising to be the most spectacular Drinktober yet!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
