<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drinktober 2022</title>
    <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Drinktober 2022</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting cosmic</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/getting-cosmic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/getting-cosmic/</guid>
      <description>A mysterious figure has been spotted in the skies! Flying through the atmosphere, wielding the Power Cosmic!
Behold the mighty Silver Drinker! Herald of Galactus: the devourer of worlds!
Herald of change and disruption!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Snot as bad </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-snot-as-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-snot-as-bad/</guid>
      <description>The good news is I’m past the snot stage and onto the vomit stage! The bad news is that has left little room for comedic #whatidowithoutthepub activities, but hopefully adventures will soon resume now I can successfully roll out of bed and to the sofa.
Today’s tipple is a feisty little cranberry juice, which is actually quite nice, with a lemsip chaser. Would be extra nice with a little vodka in there but here we all are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s only a model!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-only-a-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-only-a-model/</guid>
      <description>At long last, this epic quest has finally come to an end.
I&amp;rsquo;ve followed the mysterious red line around the map, accompanied by inspiring orchestral music, for many years but now in this cave I&amp;rsquo;ve finally found the Holy Grail!
Surely this is the cup of a coder!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping up with the Joneses</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/keeping-up-with-the-joneses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/keeping-up-with-the-joneses/</guid>
      <description>An archaeological theme for the 6th of Drinktober as Indiana Stout delves back into the hidden mysteries of the past to uncover the secrets of the Last Brewsade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everybody is Kung-Flu fighting </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/everybody-is-kung-flu-fighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/everybody-is-kung-flu-fighting/</guid>
      <description>Good news!!! I am sober and I do not fancy a drink AT ALL!!
Bad news this is primarily due to the fact I have some sort of hideous illness, currently downing lemsip as if it’s Sauvignon Blanc and dying in bed. The cats covered in snot, I coughed so hard the Alexa asked if I was ok, and my nose is as red as a walruses nutsack.
As I die quietly in bed, sober and poorly, remember to donate to an excellent cause and if you can’t donate, can somebody please make me some sort of soup and offer a rendition of soft kitty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You guava be kidding me</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/you-guava-be-kidding-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/you-guava-be-kidding-me/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re barely into the first week of Drinktober when disaster strikes.
I was planning to burn off the calories from all these beers in the gym, but somehow I&amp;rsquo;ve found myself trapped inside this insane game show.
I need to find a way to escape, but the floor is guava!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lettuce begin</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/lettuce-begin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/lettuce-begin/</guid>
      <description>After a very busy, somewhat stressful and full of flu day, ordinarily this is prime circumstances for a nice chianti and a caramel cup.
However, being a good girl observing #whatidowithoutthepub, I decided to cook a nice chicken and Caesar salad and have a vitamin water followed by a terrible film. Sadly I failed to take an appropriate photo so please enjoy the artists impression of me cooking. I also fixed the washing machine so overall sober me is a complete champ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>By Daisies Be Driven</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/by-daisies-be-driven/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/by-daisies-be-driven/</guid>
      <description>Dammit, Plantera, this beer is warm! Go get me another one!
Shocking scenes for the Fourth of Drinktober! Things are turning Fuchsia-ing Hostile as we bear witness to this Vulgar Display of Flower!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just hear meowt</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/just-hear-meowt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/just-hear-meowt/</guid>
      <description>Day three and I’m sat it’s not Cat-utday still. Or at least Friday night when I could enjoy a sweet, sweet vino.
Today was a very busy day which involved much running about and not much time to miss the pub. However, now I’m home alone, this is prime drink o’clock.
Of course, I had to distract myself and find something to fit in with #whatidowithoutthepub so I decided the only healthy thing to do was to dress up my cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheese</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/cheese/</guid>
      <description>Cheese!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I like big putts and I cannot lie</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/i-like-big-putts-and-i-cannot-lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/i-like-big-putts-and-i-cannot-lie/</guid>
      <description>I do enjoy a big putt, although this gives a different meaning to clubbing.
In today’s edition of #whatidowithoutthepub, I very much fancied some day drinking. Possibly left Over lesbian rage. However, it’s for charity innit so I decided to distract myself with my favourite competition sport, Mini Golf.
Although it’s not as fun as drunk mini golf, I did win in a spectacular fashion and looked cute doing so, so I’ll take that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaze into the beer of Dredd!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/gaze-into-the-beer-of-dredd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/gaze-into-the-beer-of-dredd/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been around since the early days you might have noticed I&amp;rsquo;m a bit of a Judge Dredd fanboy.
So when Northern Monk released a Thought Bubble Festival collaboration beer late last year with Jock, one of my favourite Dredd artists, you can be sure I snapped up a few cans quicker than you can say &amp;ldquo;I AM THE LAW!&amp;rdquo;, and couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist hanging on to one to give me a chance to break out the Judge Beerman outfit again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s here!!!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-here/</guid>
      <description>It’s here!!!! Day #1 of the glorious return of everyone’s favourite activity #drinktober
Whilst Johnny has a lovely beer, I’ve undertaken my first instalment of #whatidowithoutthepub, drinking copious Heineken Zeros at a very angry, excellent lesbian energy gig.
Side note, if you’ve never heard Bizarre Fae or Delilah Bon you absolutely should. - Heidi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s gonna be a long, long month</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-gonna-be-a-long-long-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/it-s-gonna-be-a-long-long-month/</guid>
      <description>And so it begins!
We&amp;rsquo;re literally blasting off into Drinktober as we answer the question literally nobody was asking: what if the Rocket Man was the Rocketeer?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello? Is this thing on?</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/hello-is-this-thing-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/posts/2022/hello-is-this-thing-on/</guid>
      <description>Hey all! Your friendly neighbourhood Beerman here, just kicking the tires and making sure the website&amp;rsquo;s ready to roll for another month of my booze-fuelled shenanigans!
While you&amp;rsquo;re here, why not check out the sneaky preview of some of the things to look forward to in what&amp;rsquo;s promising to be the most spectacular Drinktober yet!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
