<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>12 beers of Christmas 2020 on Drinktober 2020</title>
    <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 12 beers of Christmas 2020 on Drinktober 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s all folks</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/that-s-all-folks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/that-s-all-folks/</guid>
      <description>For the twelfth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Twelve Days original porter from Hook Norton.
And so the twelve beers of Christmas comes to an end - I hope it&amp;rsquo;s been as much fun for you guys as it has for me. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to hit the donate button on your way out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting blitzed</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/getting-blitzed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/getting-blitzed/</guid>
      <description>For the eleventh beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Blitzen Ruby Christmas Ale from Black Sheep
We&amp;rsquo;re almost at the end now, so it seems like a good time to celebrate with this famous festive special from the kebab shop - Döner and Blitzen :D</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pony play</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/pony-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/pony-play/</guid>
      <description>For the tenth day of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : My Little Sabrony from Arbor Ales
It&amp;rsquo;s been a tough old year, a bit of a &amp;lsquo;mare. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s tricky to stay stable. A little horsing around once in a while can help save you from _foal_ing apart at the seams.
If you&amp;rsquo;re still reading after those dreadful horse puns, why not hoof it over to the donation page and drop a few quid in the box?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enter the ouch mouse!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/enter-the-ouch-mouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/enter-the-ouch-mouse/</guid>
      <description>For the ninth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Pricky Back Otchan from Great Newsome Brewery
According to the label, the Pricky Back Otchan is the old Yorkshire name for a hedgehog, so naturally I had to bring out superstar hedgehog Princess Neville to take her turn in the spotlight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But I&#39;d have to charge</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/but-i-d-have-to-charge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/but-i-d-have-to-charge/</guid>
      <description>For the eighth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Off Tempo Milkshake IPA from Bad Co. brewing
Normally this milkshake IPA would bring all the boys to the yard, but due to social distancing it&amp;rsquo;s running online milkshake classes instead.
A shiny no-prize goes to the first person to identify all the &amp;ldquo;boys&amp;rdquo; on the zoom call&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is the way</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/this-is-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/this-is-the-way/</guid>
      <description>For the seventh beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Easy Now Baby NEIPA from Bad Co. Brewing
It&amp;rsquo;s the eighth day of Drinkmas - New Beer&amp;rsquo;s Eve - and I&amp;rsquo;m stretching the theme to it&amp;rsquo;s limits in a flagrant case of wanting an excuse to make a costume. Baby IPA, Baby Yoda - close enough, right!
Guest starring Selwyn as the not very convincing Grogu in an undersized cardboard pod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meow</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/meow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/meow/</guid>
      <description>For the sixth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Christmas Kitty vanilla porter from Brass Castle
That&amp;rsquo;s right, the Christmas Kitty has come to visit - that well known festive tradition that we all know about. Or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a deleted scene from the Cats movie?
Either way - meow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jingle</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/jingle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/jingle/</guid>
      <description>For the fifth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman brought to me : Jingle Bell Rock golden ale from Pennine Brewing Co.
So occasionally when people see the Beercave Christmas decorations they ask &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s with the large paper boulder with the bells glued to it?&amp;rdquo;
So I tell them : &amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s the Jingle Bell Rock!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He sees you when you&#39;re sleeping..</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/he-sees-you-when-you-re-sleeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/he-sees-you-when-you-re-sleeping/</guid>
      <description>For the fourth beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman gave to me - Evil Elf biscuity ale, from Rudgate.
 He sees you when you&amp;rsquo;re sleeping
He&amp;rsquo;s watching from his shelf
He wants to cut you inside out
So beware the Evil Elf!
 Yes, here to spread a little Christmas fear, it&amp;rsquo;s the evil elf. He&amp;rsquo;s off the shelf, off the chain, and out for blood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dej-arr vu!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/dej-arr-vu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/dej-arr-vu/</guid>
      <description>For the third beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman gave to me - Anchor Christmas Ale!
And so, from the Department of Shameless prop re-use, here&amp;rsquo;s a Christmas Anchor.
Yo-Ho-Ho-Ho!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When elves go bad</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/when-elves-go-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/when-elves-go-bad/</guid>
      <description>For the second beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman gave to me, a Bad Elf dry hop ale.
So it looks like I was one present short yesterday, and now I know why! I found this cheeky little character sitting on his shelf&amp;hellip; and he&amp;rsquo;s nicked my beer!
That&amp;rsquo;s what I call a Bad Elf!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say Merry Christmas to my little friend!</title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/say-merry-christmas-to-my-little-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/say-merry-christmas-to-my-little-friend/</guid>
      <description>For the first beer of Drinkmas, the Beerman gave to me, a White Christmas ale from Saltaire brewery.
There may not be snow on the ground, but Tony Montana here has his own ideas about how to enjoy a white Christmas&amp;hellip;
Merry Christmas, ya cock-a-roaches!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beer we go again </title>
      <link>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/beer-we-go-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drinktober.co.uk/12beers/2020/beer-we-go-again/</guid>
      <description>Well, here we are again, back between the bottle and the glue gun for a festive Drinktober special edition.
When Heidi&amp;rsquo;s not engaged in alcohol free antics, she also rules over Hull LGBT+ Community Pride, AKA Pride in Hull with her tiny iron fist - or something along those lines anyway! So when she mentioned raising funds for their 2021 event I jumped at the opportunity to drink beer and show off :)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
